Dang it!
No!
It crashed!
I ought to say found.
Looks like the game crashed.
Should the game attempt to rest... yes.
Restore it please.
Hopefully everything's fine.
Whoa!
Was not ready for that.
I have no idea if this is where I was.
I think it was.
It should be okay.
Oh my god!
I gotta get back into this.
I'm already... I'm feeling the apiocco right now.
It's the Italian term for having eaten food and after that you just feel a little bloated, you know?
I ate a tuna sandwich.
It was so good.
I couldn't eat all of it though.
It was quite a big one.
I'm saving the rest for later.
I guess
I'll go up here first.
Always explore... by the way, I had an idea while I was eating.
What if I were to... like... okay, so you start in hemisphere.
But what if I were to strictly and directly go to snowy depths, you know, via the chasm.
And just, you know, just quickly run through the area and see if I can't find a crazy wand.
Like, think about that.
Wait!
Doesn't this look weird?
Hello?
Why does it look like this?
Am I crazy?
Oh no.
Oh my god!
What?
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
I am so freaking confused right now.
Did everything fucking bug out with the crash here?
This is fucked, right?
Hold on.
I'm gonna actually... I'm gonna re-chat.
Guys, is this bugged?
Hold on.
Was I muted for all this time?
Oh, I clicked the wrong button.
Never mind.
It's fucked.
I was not muted?
Okay, perfect.
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, that sucks, man.
I don't want to play bugged.
I'm gonna restart.
Oh, that's unfortunate, man.
I don't know what else is bugged, you know?
It could be really bad.
Who knows?
I'm gonna... I wonder if that counts as a... Yeah, it does.
Of course it does.
There we go.
Yeah, I'm gonna start over.
That's unfortunate.
I guess that stuff happens.
It's fine though.
I didn't get that far either.
Like I get to coal pits and that's it, right?
Hopefully the game is not bugged from now on.
Hopefully it was only that.
That one save, you know?
So if I ever do that again, like where I have to alt-tab out of the game or like take a break, I'm actually just gonna save the game manually.
You know, like save and exit and then go back into the game when I'm ready to play again.
Just to avoid that stuff in the future.
Come on.
Did you see that?
Bounced off, came back, hit this box.
That could have been quite bad.
Get down here.
Maybe I'll try my strategy here.
Straight into snowy depths, maybe?
Is that a terrible idea?
I feel like it may be a terrible idea.
I mean, worst case, I can get back up, right?
You know what?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We gotta, let's just go normal.
I feel like that's only gonna cause more issues if I do it that way.
Like I can't kill the people there, you know?
They're gonna completely mess with me.
It's gonna be troublesome.
You there.
I cannot hit anything right now.
Oh, I want to destroy them.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, sweet.
Whoa.
Cool wizards don't look at explosions.
And that's me.
Hey miss, hey miss.
More he misses.
Man, I'm finding a lot of gold really quick.
Like the other time I had like a thousand.
This is insanity.
Also I just realized I didn't even check whether or not I have water.
I have blood.
No, I have pheromone.
Oh dude, this is the time to test this.
Sick dodge there.
Come on, man.
Where are you?
Get pheromone down.
Come on.
Hey.
Okay, he's my friend now.
So now I can just kill him.
No, I can't.
He gets mad.
Even friends get mad when you shoot them in the face.
Oh, burning so much.
Oh, this is a horrible start.
I should have used this from the beginning.
Dang it.
Okay, well pheromone strategy confirmed.
Not a good strategy.
That's something at least.
That's a lesson.
He's still here.
But he's dying from the acid or toxic sludge, I guess.
Come on now.
Die.
There we go.
You know what?
41 HP.
That's really bad start.
Oh my god.
It's fine.
I have the tablet.
The mighty tablet.
Come here.
And I need water.
I need water right now.
I can't stand looking at all this toxic sludge.
What?
Why was... Huh?
What the fuck is happening here?
Why is there a spell just hanging out?
Hold on, is my game still bugged?
That feels weird.
If you
want, I shall grab it.
Hey.
Oh yeah?
Oh my god.
No, no.
I ran out of levitation.
Shit.
There we go.
Water.
Get rid of this shit.
Even though I would love to have pheromone on me.
It's just I need water more.
Water is like so incredibly important.
That's it?
Okay.
That's fine.
In fact, we can make more.
Let's do that.
Mix it up good.
I can dig.
Worm pheromone.
Wait.
What the hell is going on in there?
I can't dig.
Wait.
What?
There's something very specific this doesn't dig through.
I don't understand.
Is it the damn rock?
Good enough.
Okay.
More.
More water.
Oh, there's a lot of toxic up there.
Where'd you come from?
He came from where I started.
The hell?
Mix.
Okay.
Nice.
I was kind of stuck there.
It was weird.
Okay.
Dead end.
I hate these dead ends at the long of these long tunnels.
So you have to walk all the way back and then down again, you know?
So annoying.
Like I bet you this is going to lead to a dead end too.
Like look, now I have to walk all the way back.
If only there was a little hole.
I mean, I could make a hole myself, I guess.
This guy right here is just the worst.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, present for you.
Oh, you know what?
Actually,
my God, he deflected the... Wow.
Fuck you, man.
Give me my tablet.
Oh no, it's right next to him.
Oh, what?
Thanks.
Come on.
No.
Fuck you.
That's how we do it.
God, I felt good.
What an asshole.
Don't even care about this guy.
Give me your money.
Thanks.
Somehow I have 600 already.
Why am I getting all this money from?
Am I really killing that many enemies?
It doesn't feel like it.
Oh, is this collapsed mines?
It's about to get dangerous as it is.
It's not a bad want.
This one right here is decent.
Like I like to hate on the bouncing burst, but right now it's actually doing pretty well.
Levitation.
I just had an idea for something.
Like I could... Hold on.
No.
Okay, we gotta leave.
We gotta leave.
Nope.
Just get out of here.
Oh, no.
Don't kill me.
Anyway, my idea is if I can go up on the tree to the west, I can grab the evil eye, right?
Or the demon eye or whatever.
And I can technically use that to dig.
Like it's a guaranteed digger.
You know, it's a G digger.
The G dig.
And that would be quite a kind of nice.
It takes through almost anything, right?
Want?
Oh, man.
I'm conflicted.
And we have a fireman.
Oh, wait.
He's in there.
That's fine.
Yeah, I don't care about that.
What's this?
No, thanks.
Okay, speaking of digging.
Solid.
Very good.
Yes, yes.
That's exactly what I need.
Fuck this worm shit.
Thanks.
Now I'm ready for the Heezy base.
Except let's just not die there on the way, you know?
Fucking any surface here can kill me.
Oh, no.
Oh, he's not gonna see me from here.
I'm safe.
Nice.
Scared to pick up that money, though?
No, I think we go 700.
That's not bad.
Heal up.
And what do we got?
Square barrier.
Long distance cast.
Could be nice if we find teleport.
Let's see.
Boomerang spells.
Eat your vegetables.
Iron stomach.
What does this do again?
You inflict more damage the more satiated you are.
But you start losing health if your stomach is empty.
If I could get both of these, they kind of synergize, don't they?
Boomerang spells?
I don't like that.
I'm gonna reroll.
There it is.
Muchas gracias.
I take it.
Now I want, I think this one, for sure.
And then I want that one.
And then I want...
Do I want square?
No.
No, I don't want that.
Do I want sea of acid?
No, of course I don't.
What the fuck do you think I am?
A psycho?
Boo.
Next.
What?
No, no, no.
Now we're talking!
Oh yeah, oh yeah, that's it.
That's our damage wand.
And then we have a digger as well.
But hold on, we also have this, which reduces castelay.
It reduces... Actually, hold on.
This one reduces recharge time as well.
Hello.
Okay, but it's not that cool.
Like, it's sort of cool.
Wait a minute.
Put this one here.
Look how fast that is.
Like, that is not bad.
This is a modifier.
What if I modify only that one?
What happens then?
Wait, is that better?
It's really hard to tell.
Hmm.
Oh wait, it's shuffle.
I'm an idiot.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Okay.
So now I affect that.
0.33.
Basically, I'm trying to make a good digging wand here.
Is that good?
Maybe I want these?
These are the bubble sparks.
I actually don't like the bubble sparks very much.
But if I can combine them with the digging bolts...
Wait, no, wait, it doesn't work like that.
Wait, does it?
No, no, it doesn't work like that.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean, this is for sure our first wand.
I mean, that's solid.
That's good.
I'm not gonna change that.
It is what it is.
The next one, it's gonna be digging.
Let's see if we can make the fastest.
That's pretty fast.
That's slow.
Slow, but hold on.
Oh, we're limited by recharge?
Yeah.
But on this one...
Dum, dum, dum, dum.
I don't... hmm.
Why does this create a big spark?
Like a bright spark, but this one doesn't.
Oh, is that kind of that?
Oh yeah, it is.
Okay, weird.
Yeah, okay.
Put it here.
That's our digger.
That's our gold digger.
Digging for gold, basically, is what we're doing now.
And then we want... I don't think I want anything else.
Is that crazy?
I mean, I could try something, but I need a trigger.
I wanted to put...
Wait, this is blood?
Never mind.
I thought it was the lightning thing.
Okay, I guess we're out of here.
I'm gonna leave these up here so I can replace these wands without losing the spells.
Oh, but wait a minute!
We have tinker with wands everywhere.
It doesn't matter.
That's fantastic.
That means I don't have to anger any gods at any time.
It's actually so freeing, you know?
It's a big deal.
I need to take a sip here.
Oh yeah.
Oh, what a glorious Sunday it is.
And you shall die.
This is a great spell.
I like this spell.
Come on.
Okay, fine.
I have to remember, this one shoots around corners.
Shh, round a corner.
Oh!
Time for the test.
Not bad.
I mean, considering the fact that this is stone.
Decent.
Heck yeah!
Good start.
Let's not die to something stupid now.
That's pretty much the only thing I need to not do.
Do not.
How fast does this dig here?
Oh my god.
Oh yeah baby!
Gold galore!
I've struck gold!
Give me water.
And we also have the tablet for emergency situations.
This is great.
I like this.
Like this?
No problem.
I dig through it.
No idea where I'm even going.
And that's the beauty of it.
Uh, this guy wants a piece of me but he's not gonna get it.
Is that electricity I just saw?
What just happened there?
Oh, hold on.
Hey.
Can we please destroy this?
There we go.
Oh no.
Sweet.
Now we turn this into water.
The problem is I don't have a good mixer.
You know what?
Having a digging wand is actually such a game changer.
Maybe I should make that one of my biggest priorities.
Just being able to go like anywhere almost is such a big deal.
It's wild.
Like I can even dig through this.
It's actually really nice.
That was a little bit sketchy.
That was sketchy.
Everything's fine though.
I'm okay.
Everything is A-O-K.
Is that?
Oh, it's a slime.
With a bit of toxic.
Let's not dig like that then.
I'm gonna go here.
What's up dude?
Oh no.
I should have seen that coming.
Damn it.
Why do I always do this shit?
I knew that was gonna happen.
Destroy it.
All right, fine.
What's that?
Lava?
That's in the treasure chest?
Do we really want that?
I don't think I want that man.
Keep it.
I'm getting in here.
Oh, that's right.
This thing shoots through walls.
I really need to abuse that.
Give me all that gold on the way out.
Lovely.
660 gold.
That's almost very demon.
Okay, that was the right side.
At least some of it.
Time for the left.
Come on man.
This guy is really eager.
Digging bolt is potentially one of the best digging spells.
Like, if you have the right one for it and it can dig fast enough, you know what I mean?
Like, you can really make this shit good.
Whoa!
Ah!
Nice.
This is not even as fast as it goes.
You can definitely make this faster.
Like, you've had a chainsaw I can put on this?
Make it shoot even faster?
Or shoot?
You know what I mean.
Okay.
Already at 900.
Sir?
He went down with the ship.
What a dumbass.
Dumbass!
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god.
I somehow got hit.
So annoying.
I tell you, I think I hate slime more than I hate fire.
Oh, this thing is annoying because it doesn't actually...
Ah!
What, what, what, what, what?
What do I... Oh, I don't have anything else really.
I'm not quite sure what to do here.
I hit him there.
Hey, there we go.
It's wildly inaccurate.
Got it.
Yep.
Kind of funny how it just becomes inert.
It doesn't disappear, you know?
Hello?
That's not bad.
Fuck yeah, man.
That may even be quite decent, actually.
Oh, I'm gonna leave you in there.
How about that?
I do not care to release you.
Ah, let me go this way.
I love digging.
Oh, there's a bunch of gold there.
Also, I just remembered that we have this that just made me really happy.
Like, if I find a wand, we can... I mean, I can... I can change them now.
It's crazy.
Changes the whole gameplay.
Okay, give me that.
All right, that's fine.
Let's get out of here.
Good.
Hello?
Thanks.
Okay, now we're back at the start, so let's go in the middle.
We've gone left and right.
Now it's down.
Solid fucking spell this is.
I forget the name of it.
What's it called?
Chain Bolt.
Love you, Chain Bolt.
I love Chain Bolt and I love Usain Bolt.
I'm in a bit of silly mood.
Give me this one.
Hey, I hit two with... Ah, no!
Prepare the surface.
There we go.
Now we mix.
This one doesn't mix very well.
There we go.
Man, we're at 53 HP.
Ah, we got to be a little careful here.
That's too low for my taste.
It may be time to get out, you know?
Oh my lord, look at that.
It looks like something I don't want no part of.
It's a whole different gameplay.
Like, I can see an enemy go like, nah, I don't want to fight that.
I'm just gonna dig away.
Oh, I see.
Pixels of lava.
I'd rather have a big pool of lava than small pixels of it.
At least I know where it is then.
Small pixels can be a pain.
What do we got here?
Oh, not much.
Maybe I'm going a little too nuts here with the digging.
But it's fun, man.
So much fun.
The freedom is unmatched.
Almost 2k gold.
This is wild.
I'm gonna be rerolling perks so much, you don't even know.
But maybe that's a bad strategy in the long run to do that.
Or maybe it isn't.
Money you can always acquire, right?
Perks are like, limited.
You can't keep getting perks.
At some point, the perks stop.
And there's no more.
So you gotta get the best perks you can, right?
So I think it makes sense to collect a lot of money.
With the intention of rerolling a lot.
Whoop.
See, you would think this is a dead end, but it's not.
Hehehe.
Not for me!
Oh yeah.
I'm like a little... I don't know what the English word is, but those things that are in your backyard always crawling onto the earth.
Popping up here and there.
Gopher is maybe the word.
And Danish is Mulvap.
Oh, that's a chest.
Nice!
Lovely stuff.
We need some more of that.
We need more of that energy.
Chest energy.
But I guess that you could make an argument that collecting all the money right now is kind of a waste, because later on, you will collect so much money compared to this.
Like, 2000 isn't even that much.
Then maybe it's not worth it to do now, but later on it is, you know?
So I can definitely see the argument there.
Like, you can make that argument.
So yeah, let's just, let's actually hit the head out now.
Let's just grab some gold on the way, and then we're gonna head out.
Oh wait, I'm... Let's not fucking drown.
That would be a terrible way to go.
All right, let's go.
Although, wait a minute, we are in the coal pits.
No, no, no.
I was about to say, let's go to Funko Caverns.
With 50 HP?
No, no, no, no.
We're not doing that.
Nope.
We played safe.
195 HP is not bad.
All right.
Boo.
Disgusting.
Repelling cape.
And this is why we have money.
Fungal disease.
Would be really funny to take this one too.
I wonder which one cancels which.
Like, if I take this, I can't tinker, but then I have this.
So can I tinker?
Or can I not tinker?
I... I need to take this.
Holy shit.
Yes, sir.
We need to find extra perks.
Speaking of limited perks, anything that can make that problem a little easier on us is very welcome.
And we don't need to edit anything right now.
We don't care.
So honestly, we just... Nah, do we want to buy something here?
Hold on.
Maybe there's a good wand.
So the way I judge a good wand, low cast delay, low recharge time.
Big mana, big mana charge speed.
And no shuffle.
And then spells cast is one.
That's how I judge it.
And then maybe also spread.
I don't really look at the spread, actually.
I should look at the spread.
So like this one, I would say is a C.
This one sucks.
Shuffle is immediately F.
This one is D plus in my mind.
Like this one is not bad.
It is bad because of mana charge speed is super low.
I don't like any of these.
I hate it.
We move on.
All right.
And look at this.
Wands galore.
Enemies also.
A mysterious darkness.
Oh, wait, I know what it means now.
It's literally a darkness.
I get it.
Literally a darkness.
Look around me.
It's darker than usual.
That's basically what that means.
Okay, well, well, well.
This is going to work.
It's going to take a while, but it's fine.
Maybe we don't stand here.
Oh, he went that way.
There we go.
Firecrackers, short range homing.
Yeah, here's the thing.
Thanks.
I will take that.
These things?
Nah, I hate it.
In fact, let's put the stuff we don't want on trash wands like this.
Oh, is this a trash wand?
I think it is.
I don't like the firecracker.
Firecracker makes me angry.
But it is actually not bad.
Hold on.
Maybe it is not bad.
If I can live with the firecracker, what does it do exactly?
Makes it protect how to release firecrackers when it disappears.
Nope, I don't like it.
I hate it, so we're going to throw it out.
Get rid of that one.
I will take that one thing from it and that's it.
Let me look at the other one.
Oh, look how fast I take through ice.
Yes!
Speed up for me, baby.
The rest?
Don't care.
Actually, maybe I'll take that.
I don't care about the rest.
Sweet stuff.
Let's go left, huh?
I don't like this mysterious darkness.
I would say it's too mysterious for me.
Also, oh wait, this is a shuffle.
Does this actually affect this?
I don't think so.
Hey, now that's what I'm talking about.
Yes, sir.
I love that.
0.15, 0.3.
I like it.
0.1, 0.0.
Hold on.
Oh, even better.
But somehow there's no sound on it now.
What?
Hold on.
Is this sound?
Hold on, I'm going to restart my game.
I feel like the sound is bugged.
Shouldn't do that.
Sometimes the sound box in this game and I have to restart.
Okay, that's weird.
I guess it just doesn't make a sound.
It just feels odd to dig and not have a sound, you know.
Holy crap!
That was a headshot right in between my eyes.
The coup de grace.
Except I would have been dead if that was the case.
I've been listening to that album quite a bit.
It feels good, man.
This darkness is throwing me off because I feel like I haven't discovered an area.
Then I go there and like, oh yeah, I have discovered it.
Actually annoying.
But look at this.
Uh, can I?
No!
Shit!
I can't get in there.
I gotta find a black hole or a plasma cutter or something to that effect.
That's not bad.
I mean, hold on, 0.08.
0.3.
Nope.
Ah, it's better to... this one is just better.
Let's wait a bit.
Uh oh.
Wow, that's scary.
Somehow I did not get hit there.
That was a miracle.
No idea what happened.
I guess I'm gonna have to make the sound effects for this.
Probably a bit more digging sound.
This is a bit too high tech sounding.
Hey!
A heart for me!
Poink.
I'm not gonna get that.
I have enough money.
Oh!
Exquisite me?
How dare you, sir?
Ah!
I'm beset on all sides.
Don't you beat me.
Sir, do not... me, okay?
Or I will... you.
You understand me?
Alright, that's annoying.
I gotta take care of the big guy.
Ah, he's gonna keep spawning these.
I feel like my weapon is not suited for this.
Wow.
Stop it!
Ah, there we go.
If I get close enough with this weapon, I can actually hit the things, the little projectiles it makes, and the big guy at the same time.
That's the strategy with this spell.
Look at the look of that wand!
That looks cool!
I do like this spell, Sonnet.
We can use a bunch of these now.
Why not?
Sure.
But I want the old wand back.
There we go.
Thanks!
Much appreciated.
Okay.
I hate this vapor.
It's just... I have to sit here and wait, you know?
Unless I have a teleport wand.
Then I can get past it.
Ouch!
What's this?
Pherom?
I already have Pheromone.
Wait a minute!
I actually see Heezy people here.
Maybe there is a healer in here somewhere.
Let's keep an eye out for that.
Okay, I see.
I can't tell if I've been here.
I have been here, but it's not obvious because of the mysterious darkness.
So mysterious.
Blood potion?
No, thanks.
Nice.
That guy... He was out in the cold for too long.
So there's a guy up here somewhere.
He's quite far away, it seems.
I can't dig through here, unfortunately.
Oh, he's very far away.
I'm not gonna get to him.
Not with my current getup.
Uh, nope.
Okay.
I don't know where I'm going.
And you know what?
I like it.
Just dig.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
Look at that.
We made it to the... Ooh, I actually know where we are.
Wait a minute!
Ah, but we can't get through dense rock.
I was about to say we can go grab that heart.
But we need something better to dig with.
Like a laser plasma cutter thingy.
Don't have it though.
Okay, I've been here.
It's so annoying that I can't tell where I've been.
This is like my one weakness among some others.
Okay, let's go, uh, let's go say hi to that guy in here.
I'm not afraid.
Just keep dodging.
Hey, that works!
Beautiful.
Oh my god!
That's not a fair assholes.
Am I hitting?
Okay.
Oh my god.
Sir.
Stop it.
I beg of you.
Slimey.
What is this again?
Oh, wait, that just spawns like a friendly creature.
Right?
Let me double...
nah, I'm not gonna double check.
I know that's the case.
So these guys, I need to get close.
Yeah, see, here he comes.
There we go.
Oh god.
This is a disaster.
Please don't die.
Oh, Jesus.
Fuck.
We're getting out.
It's over.
Or maybe not.
I will take that.
Uh, get rid of this shit.
Thanks.
Tell me I can get out here.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Hey, assholes.
Oh, no.
Wow.
Yeah, we gotta dig.
Where am I now?
Yes.
Close one.
That was a bit too close, though.
Okay, what do we got?
Nothing that seems very cool at first glance, I have to admit here.
Maybe that one accelerating shot.
But not, don't buy it yet.
Let's go see the perks.
And now we have one more.
Oh, that's healthy exploration?
Oh, that sounds not that good.
Vampirism!
Ooh, man, I'm conflicted.
I don't know.
I already did re-roll a bunch.
I think I had to go with Vampirism, man.
We gotta be able to heal.
That's the main thing.
It's so important.
Now, the only issue is we are now in Heezy Base and I have nothing to my name.
It's really bad.
I don't have anything.
We need something.
Something drastic.
Like a good piece of soil.
That's what we need.
It's not actually what we need.
But it could be.
Is that doing any difference?
It does 30 damage.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
Why does it do 30?
It does 25.
Say what?
That's weird.
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Oh, that's not fair.
It doesn't help that I have no damage.
It's aiming for the statue.
Oh, my lord.
Okay, that guy escaped quick, huh?
We've got wands at least.
That's pretty cool.
I like that.
I like the wands.
What's happening in there, guys?
Thank God he can't come in here.
Okay, that works.
Sweet.
Get out of here.
Yeah.
I'm stuck.
I gotta dig my way out.
Diggity diggity diggity.
Oh, I can drink this.
What?
Why am I not healing?
Wait a minute.
Am I not drinking?
Oh, now it works.
Oh, that was weird.
What?
So, I can't drink this blood?
Oh, that's really... Okay, now I can.
Oh, that's weird.
What the hell?
Okay, it's a bit awkward the way that works.
Look at this.
Isn't that beautiful?
I think it is.
And a chest for me.
Thanks.
I actually kind of need it.
Forgot that the vampirism actually took off 25% of my HP.
So, that means it's actually better to take this early, right?
Before you find health.
So, now I'm maybe okay glad that I didn't find that many hearts before now.
Not bad.
And we have this broken wand for in here.
Oh, there's exciting times ahead.
Are you ready, kids?
What's up, dude?
Oh, he spawns enemies.
Yeah.
How dare you?
Oh, this shoots through this thing.
That's actually a sick strategy right there.
Get rid of that oil.
Being flammable is not what I desire to be.
I gotta say, the chain bolt is doing decent work in here, except for the turrets and all that.
Other than that, it's actually not bad.
Wow.
This is kind of cool.
Large spitter bolt, huh?
Do I want that?
It's shuffled though.
0.10, 0.07.
No, I don't think I want it.
Nah.
Actually, no, no, no, I don't want it.
I don't want it.
Uh-oh.
Let's get rid of that first.
One at a time, guys.
Come up here.
Uh-oh, not this.
Wait.
Was this shot a lot slower than usual just now?
That was weird.
It was, like, really slow down.
Oh, god.
Do I have anything better to do?
Oh, you know what?
Maybe I'll shoot magic missiles at him.
Holy, that's way better.
That's way better.
I gotta save the magic missiles for these guys.
That's how we do it.
Oh, be careful here.
Sweet.
Let me have this dude.
Nice.
And look at all that juicy blood, baby.
All I see is health.
But all my blood is on fire.
That makes me...
Friend?
Friendo.
Who needs blood?
Not me.
Hopefully, this, uh, chain pull is not gonna automatically go towards my friendo.
That's a bar.
Hold on.
Heal me.
Fuck.
It killed him.
Ah, that is what it is.
Would be pretty OP to just have him follow me around everywhere and heal me, right?
But I will eat this delicious blood.
So good.
198, baby.
What are you guys drinking?
Having a bit of a nightcap.
The evil lair.
That is the easy base.
Why are you guys evil?
Why are you evil?
Whoa.
Oh, look at all these potions though.
Flammox.
Ooh.
That one was flammable.
Gold.
Oh, man.
Okay.
There we go.
Flammoxium is being poured on me.
I don't like it.
Hey, friendo.
No, friendo.
No, friendo got turned into a battle.
I hate that.
Not a fan of that.
But I am a fan of this blood.
Eat it all.
Drink some blood.
Nothing satiates you like the blood of your enemies.
Oh, yeah.
Don't touch them.
Okay.
We're fine.
That was a friend.
I killed them by accident.
Damn it.
Oh, man.
The flammoxium really is flammoxing or flummoxing.
I feel flummoxed.
I do feel flummoxed.
What the hell is that?
Liquid vacuum field.
Teleport.
Yo.
Thanks.
What's this?
Sucks liquid materials nearby and releases them upon expiring.
What?
Sucks liquid.
I gotta try that immediately.
That sounds intriguing AF.
Uh, toxic.
You know, let's find a better place.
Let's try.
Let's try this water.
Oh, yeah.
Huh.
Weird.
Okay.
Why though?
Why would I want to do this?
Let's see.
Huh.
I mean, it's cool as hell that it works like that.
Really nice.
But why?
Why would I do?
I can't immediately see a reason.
Maybe there's a good reason.
Friendo!
Wait, is he actually gonna do anything to me?
I guess he doesn't have a weapon.
He only has a healing thingy.
Dang it.
Okay, so here's the plan.
You're my friend.
Come here.
Oh, yeah.
You can heal me.
That's fine.
But come here.
Follow me.
Now that I have a teleport, I am gonna...
Uh, dude, watch this.
I have a genius idea.
Ah, I'm flummoxed.
I'm okay now.
Come up here.
Oh, wait.
He's not an enemy anymore.
Oh, he's still gonna follow me though.
He thinks he's gonna hurt me, but he's not because he doesn't have anything to hurt me with.
Come here.
Come here, buddy.
We're going on an adventure.
Yes, come here.
That's a good boy.
I'm gonna call you Syphilis, the third.
Oh, wrong way.
This way, Sif.
That's his nickname.
Come here.
And then we go up here.
Oh, yeah.
Come here now.
Eh.
Hey!
I protect you.
Come.
Come up here.
Is he gonna follow me?
He is.
Okay, so how am I gonna do this?
Uh, hold on.
I need something.
Wait a minute.
Ah, I need telekinetic kick.
That's what I need.
Basically, my plan is to get him in here and then somehow teleport out of here and put a barrel in between us so he can't follow me.
Come in here.
Come here.
You're gonna get all the way over here.
That's right.
Dude, I'm getting that pooping feeling now because of this.
Oh, look, he's walking.
That's so cute.
Come here.
All the way in the back.
My theory is that if I can outrun him quick enough with my teleport, he's gonna lose aggro on me and he's just gonna wander in here.
Come on.
All the way in the back.
Yes, that's it, boy.
See ya!
Okay, there's no way he follows me now, right?
He totally lost aggro on me.
I kind of want to check these wands out.
Hopefully, I didn't wander into his aggro range just now.
Nice!
That's actually really nice.
And the wand is also not bad either.
Look at this.
Point one.
No shuffle.
Decent mana max and charge speed.
I like it.
Sir, sir, sir, sir.
Stop that.
Um, in fact, I just threw away the wand that I usually use to kill you with, so...
One second, one second.
I'll be right there.
There we go.
Now we can talk.
Put this stuff up here because that's nice.
I do enjoy that.
And then put this one away.
Do I keep this wand?
Point, oh wait.
No, this is better, I think.
No, it's not because it only has two slots.
But I will take the spells.
That one.
Then give me...
Remove that one, sure.
And then I'll take this one instead.
Thank you!
Wait, did I do it right?
Yeah, I did.
Okay, um, good.
Now I question whether or not we can make something really cool with what we've got.
The chainsaw is nice.
Add some speed up to the spells.
Let's see what's on this one.
Giga disc projectiles, kind of want to play with those, but only if we find melee immunity.
I am scared to death of these things.
But I will take electric... Dude, I swear to god, Tinker with Wands is an insane perk!
Because you just go around and you pick up the best of the best and leave behind the rest.
How is that not best in slot?
Put this down here.
You don't want that.
Maybe I put something on this temporarily here.
That's my killer of the turrets.
The turret killer!
Look at this chair.
Happy Sunday, people.
Nothing like relaxing on a beautifully made, handcrafted, easy chair.
I dug my way into my own getting hurt.
That was amazing.
I'm gonna drink blood.
Hey!
Not only is the easy chair well made and crafted, it also withstands bullets so you can use it as a personal shield.
Lovely craftsmanship.
It's the heezy miller of chairs.
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We need this.
That's what I'm talking about.
What's up, nerds?
How you doing?
Snipers have a decent amount of HP.
I think around 60.
Maybe 50, actually.
Sneeper.
Ah, look at this guy.
He wants a piece of me.
Or maybe we're just going about his day patrolling, you know.
Came in to work, checked in, clocked in at the heezy... Oh!
That's what I'm looking for!
Fantastic!
We can definitely make something now, right?
Oh, wait.
Why did I put all my... shit.
Where's all my spark bolts?
Damn it.
Well, I guess I'd have a triplicate.
We could do something with that.
So this is probably the best candidate for this.
If I go with a good old... let's see...
damage... on that.
So that's going to do that.
That's cool.
But then we add this.
That's the... oh, wait.
I'm limited by recharge.
Okay, so we can reduce recharge with this!
But then if we change it up a bit, then sometimes things...
do it differently.
It's weird how that works.
But actually, now the damage effect applies to this.
So what we really need is something like a double spell.
Something like that.
That's not bad, I think.
And then if we add a speed up...
pretty cool.
Kind of want to reduce spread somehow.
I mean, that's pretty dope.
Let's see how much damage that does to one of these mechanical enemies.
Or this guy.
A 30.
That's pretty much as much as my chain bolt makes in one shot.
This has potential to be a lot better.
Just at first glance here.
Oh yeah, baby!
Don't get flummox now.
What is this place?
All right, I'm not so sure.
I mean, it's definitely higher DPS against these guys.
It's just... they knock them back quite a bit, so it's hard to sustain the damage.
You know, I mean, we have great potential though with the spells we have to make something later.
In fact, even going back to the holy mountain right now could be sick.
What's with this growth here?
So what's that?
Pheromone?
No, what is that?
Oh, it is pheromone.
Okay.
I kind of want to get rid of this.
I do not like the plants.
Burn it all!
Lovely.
What was that sound?
Going...
Speed digging.
That's wood.
I can dig through that.
It's so weird.
I wand.
Freezing gaze, my beloved, but I need unlimited spells for that.
Double spell?
Yes, sir.
I will take all of this.
Thank you.
For later.
Wait, how good is this wand?
It's not super good.
The mana charge speed kind of sucks.
I like this relaxing music.
Makes me feel good.
Ah, he's annoying.
Oh, we got a wild.
Got a wild boy here.
I'm eating all the blood here.
What are you spawning?
Don't even think about it.
Look at all this blood.
Infinite healing.
Vampirism is sick.
Actually, such a... wait.
Huh, okay.
That makes me uneasy.
Stop bugging out like that.
That scares me.
Dude, imagine if the world, like the real world, had like bugs, you know, like physics bugs, where a rock would go a little wild.
It would fucking, you know, shake in the corner.
And if it just accidentally bugged out a little bit and launched towards you.
Holy shit, that would be so scary knowing that could happen.
Imagine.
And now we can heal a bit more because we found the heart.
Lovely stuff right there.
Vampirism is actually wild.
Okay, look at this bed.
Eat it.
Eat the bed.
Man, of all things, I would love a heart the most.
I'm just cheesing these guys right here.
Don't care.
Oh, that looks a little bit sketchy to me.
Not sure I like the look of that.
This works nice.
The way it goes through all the enemies is actually pretty sweet.
So I actually have a question here.
If I had this in front, I wonder if that's going to add 10 more damage to every single time the projectile goes through enemies.
If that is the case, then it may actually be really nice there.
Wait, what?
Why did he just die in one shot?
Oh, because I hit him from the other side before.
That's why.
That is why.
It's not a big mystery.
It is not.
I did not hit her.
I did not.
Oh, hi, Mark.
What have we got in here?
Any secrets for me to find?
No secrets.
Why are secrets just the best?
Love secrets.
This chair right here is not made up to easy standards.
He needs to get rid of.
Who brought this shit in here?
We have standards here in the Heezy base.
We need all metal chair construction only.
Get rid of that.
Hey, sir, you're there.
Thanks.
Like this is what I'm talking about.
Look how sturdy that is.
That's quality.
I'm just destroying all their property.
And I love it.
Whoa.
Am
I out of mana?
Why is it so slow?
I'm on fire.
That's okay, though.
Because I'm just going to drink the blood and be back on top.
Don't catch fire.
Nice.
This song is so relaxing.
Makes me want to take a nap in the Heezy base.
Become one with the Heezians.
You know, learn their customs and all their ways.
I want to hang out at the bar they have, you know, Friday after work, after having done evil things in the lab, just go there, crack open a cold one with the boys.
Sounds lovely.
I'm going to get in here.
Hey, it's the FBI.
Open up.
We have been found guilty of evilry.
Um, no, thanks.
I do not enjoy that wand.
That wand does not fill me up with joy.
Thank you.
I have a lot of money, actually.
And you know what?
I need to go to the bottom, right?
No, no, no.
friendo, friendo, friendo.
I need to use this instead.
So don't accidentally kill my friend.
Look at that.
He's healing me mid combat.
No, he's not.
Never mind.
No, don't die friend.
Come on, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Shit.
I mean, now that I really need it right now, let's be honest, He's healing him now.
Hey, you're on my side.
Hey, come on.
There we go.
Look at that.
Not that I really need it, because I have all this blood, you know.
I am... Dude, I am flowing and healing!
It's overflow.
Oh, he's not healing me anymore now?
Okay, that's fine.
I wonder if I can eat the enemies alive.
I kind of want to do that.
What the hell is all this?
Oh, wait.
I'm drowning.
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I don't trust any of these.
Okay.
I think those guys were enemies.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
This is a bit sketchy.
Yeah, just use this.
What's up, fools?
You want some too?
I'm not afraid of fire.
Just a bit.
What?
Wait, am I burning?
What's happening?
What?
Eat the... There we go.
Yes, there we go.
Beautiful.
Every single point of healing matters.
I just drank some oil, I think.
Oh, this guy is going to get messed up.
You need to be at the exact right point for this to work through the wall.
There we go.
Now, if only that fire would stop, then I would be very happy.
Doesn't look like it's going to stop, though.
Chaotic polymorphine?
I don't want to mess with that.
Instead, I'm just going to gently go this way.
And then, very importantly, whenever you pass this little pool of blood, you have to go...
It's very important.
It's in the Heezy Rulebook.
Okay, now we drink some more blood, because we lost a lot.
I accidentally ate his organs.
That's okay.
It's part of the job.
Get this one as well.
There we go.
I will never have healing issues, at least not in this level.
Why am I randomly taking damage?
Am I eating poison?
See, I can't drink while I'm underwater, it seems.
So I need to be above water, with blood below me, for the eating to happen.
See, right now I can do it.
Very slow, but it works.
What's that?
Oh, it's part of the chest.
The fake chest?
The fest.
Okay.
Portal detected.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Oh!
Yeah, just, you know, get rid of that.
I don't trust it.
There we go.
That's gonna explode.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, that's not what I wanted.
Turn me back.
Turn me back!
Hee, hee, hee, hee.
Man, must suck to beat these guys, they're so slow.
I do fly around, though.
There we go.
Now I eat a bit more.
Come on, man, show me some more hearts.
Show me the love.
Please.
That's for you.
No, wait, that's a friendo!
Oh, my friendo's burning.
I save you!
I save us!
Psst, there we go, there we go, buddy.
You're afraid to go.
Ow, ow, ow.
I have to remember, I have teleport.
I keep forgetting I have teleport.
Oh, I killed friendo.
Oh, I almost fell in the portal.
The strategy with those guys is to attack from one angle first, and then come from the other angle so they don't have time to rotate.
Oh, wait a minute, that's not good.
That was about to be real bad, what I just...
Ah, look at this!
Heart!
Heart for me!
The game was showing me the love, I just wasn't paying attention to the love being shown.
Ah, wait a minute, we got a...
Nice.
Ah, friendo!
Ah, oh, there's another one, okay.
I'll leave him alive.
Now, do that, thank you.
Come with me, friendo.
I wonder if Syphilis is still alive in my base.
Ah!
God damn it.
Hey.
Okay, fine.
He shot his friend.
I need to find more pheromone, actually.
I'm running low on it.
Oh, he's healing me, he's healing me.
Oh, he did.
Aw, that's so sad.
Okay, oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, I get in anywhere.
Backstage passes.
And now I drink.
The act of drinking the enemy's blood is not only for utility and healing, but it is also a sort of ritual of sorts.
By ingesting the blood of your enemies, you become thy enemy and you know thy enemy and you will be a better fighter.
Drink it all.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
Mmm, delicious.
That thing's gonna go boom, boom.
Boom, boom, boom.
Welcome to my room.
There's a chest.
Hey, sir.
Nice, I'm getting good at dealing with these guys.
Yeah, shoot the thing.
Noob.
Did you see that?
The propane tank accelerated so fast.
That it killed them in flight, just from the momentum.
That shit is amazing.
Love it.
I wonder where it went and where it exploded.
It must have gone off somewhere.
Also, there was a chest.
Let's get it.
There.
I can get that.
Easy peasy.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get in there.
Oh!
That became a little scary, just right there.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's calm down.
Wait, is he spawning healers?
Shoot, shoot.
No, he's not.
Wait, is it random?
It is random when he spawns.
Okay.
Interesting.
I thought it was predetermined that he always spawns the same one and then the next type of that enemy spawns another enemy but always the same one.
Getting a little low here.
Also, that chest is burning.
Wait, what's happening?
That thing's going to explode.
Yeah, it's exploding any second.
Now, there we go.
Drink, drink the blood.
Am I putting out the fire as well by eating it?
I'm a fire spitter.
I inhale fire.
What is it with these chests not opening?
248 HP.
Not bad, I would say.
I don't know why I'm playing so careless.
Is that psychological trick again where everything is going so nicely and you have healing so you start to play less safe, you know?
It's a bad practice to get into and I need to stop right now.
No more playing unsafe.
I mean, of course, I'm still going to take damage, but I'm going to try my utmost to act like I can't heal at all.
This is the sort of stuff I would do if I couldn't heal.
You know, just chill here for a second, shoot these guys and then slowly move on.
This guy is admiring the well-built and sturdy chair as much as me.
Unfortunately, he has to go.
That guy chose this very shitty chair, so he definitely needs to go.
What's over here?
Nothing.
Okay.
Can I get in there?
I definitely can.
Look at this.
This is the utility shaft.
Oh, no, I can't.
Okay, okay, fine, fine.
Thought I was being cute there.
Wasn't very cute, it seems.
I could go that way.
I kind of... I kind of steered away from my original mission.
I just stay on the right side first.
In fact, let me go all the way down to the portal and then go right.
No, wait a minute, no.
Let's take care of this place.
You see, he took like three seconds to turn the turret.
Now I'm far immune.
So lovely.
Let me go all the way down now.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
Fuck, I can't get in.
I have nothing.
Is there really nothing here that...
Oh, no.
Shit, okay, we definitely got to find something to get in there.
I want that heart so bad.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do I have long distance?
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, man.
I completely forgot about that.
Oh, we're back, baby.
I've missed this.
That's what I'm talking about.
Now we heal more.
Max HP has been increased.
Oh, wait, I'm taking damage when I eat this.
Wait, what am I taking damage from?
Oh, I'm poisoned.
I see, I see.
I guess I ate something I shouldn't have.
Keep drinking the blood, baby.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm back to being able to go anywhere I want.
Feels amazing, yo.
Let's still be careful, though.
Do not play over here.
What's this?
Yo, that's... What the hell is that?
Hold on, hold on.
Plate safe.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
Yeah, you ain't... Ah, okay, you are something.
Next.
Syphilis, come to my rescue.
I call upon you.
Syphilis is the guy in the van with the computer guiding me, you know?
I have a headset on.
He's back at base.
Chillin'.
Come on.
There it is.
Boink, boink, boink.
Boom, boom, boom.
I want you in my room.
Now that song is on my head or on my mind.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's a disease now.
And those are the only lyrics I know.
I don't know the rest.
That just scared me.
I have now become part of the tribe.
Day 62.
They still don't know who I am.
I'm staying here until it's safe.
Boink.
There we go.
And now...
for my next trick.
Don't trust any of that.
Wait, what?
Ouch.
You know what?
Spamming them like that is actually not a bad idea because they get stunned for every hit.
And they have trouble aiming when they're stunned.
Wait, I can...
Yo, I can eat the snow.
That's actually a legit way to get through snow if you don't have any other means.
That's awesome.
New tactic discovered.
And it's quite effective too.
I was eating that fast.
Let's drink this blood while we wait.
We'll have a sip...
of the old comrades.
Oh, we're at the edge.
So technically, we should just be going down now to find the... the anvil.
Yeah.
Look at me, man!
Fucking pro at this game.
Oh my god, I'm losing HP here.
Watch this.
This is the hot swap.
Insano style.
The hot swap.
Love the hot swap.
Okay, switch back.
Doing.
No, no, no, no.
There we go.
And I just need to make a keybind somehow to switch those two out immediately.
Okay, let's go.
Let's see.
What is that?
Another quantum split.
What happens if you quantum split a quantum split?
That's what I'm wondering.
That's not bad at all.
That's a great looking wand right there.
In fact, I may just utilize it.
Let's throw this on the floor.
I threw it on the ground.
This one, give me that back.
Put this here.
Throw this away.
Take this wand.
Now, point two, point three two.
We have a lot of slots now.
Let's see.
Okay, not bad.
But what if I do this?
Pretty cool.
But what if I were to do this?
Huh?
We do that, that, and that.
Yeah, that will do the trick.
There we go.
That is lovely.
Oh, isn't that lovely?
That's beautiful.
And then we add a little bit of short-range homing to this bastard as well.
And now those bastards home in on the enemy.
But wait.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Hold on now.
Why is it yellow?
Why isn't this being red?
Hopefully the damage plus is affecting this in the way that I hope it is.
Also, what if I were to do this instead?
What happens then?
It's a little slower.
So this is the way to go, I guess.
Oh, wait, wait.
Was that even faster?
That's even...
Wait, what did I change?
What did I just change?
What if I do this?
Okay.
Bad.
Castelay plus adds projectile speed.
Yeah, I don't like that.
I don't like that I run out of mana so fast.
We need to find the plus mana for sure.
That's the way.
But what if I were to do this?
Okay, that looks pretty sick.
I run out of mana fast.
That's the only thing.
Oh, this one cost a lot of mana.
Never mind, that's why.
Oh, that's way better now.
This one costs 10 actually.
Doesn't cut down on much, but...
That's fine, I think.
Yeah, we're good, baby.
We're good.
We could even put this on.
Do I need to put this on?
Wait a minute.
Is that even faster?
Let's take it off.
I think it's the same.
This is great, though.
I'm loving that.
This can go to hell now.
This is good.
And what do we need?
You know what, let's do this.
Let's do...
What could we do for our...
I guess digging.
We need digging.
Digging is good.
We can make it faster, no?
No!
Don't throw it down there.
That's way too slow.
But what if I were to take one of these?
Because that thing is still fast.
As it is.
We don't need two of these.
Heck yeah, dude.
So now...
Wait.
Wait, dude.
No?
Oh, okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Oh, it's the wrong one.
I'm an idiot.
What does that feel like?
Doesn't feel great.
Doesn't feel great either.
Feels better.
Can we do...
I don't even know, man.
I do want to quantum split this guy right there.
But recharge rate is the problem here.
Maybe I want to put this on this instead.
And then this up here.
That's way too slow.
Like that.
That's somehow still... Wait, what?
Oh, wrong one.
I think that's still the best.
Is that crazy?
No, no, wait.
This is definitely faster.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it.
I found it.
That's what we're going to do.
And then for the last one, for my last trick, we're going to do absolutely nothing.
That's right.
We're going to do absolutely nothing.
On which we go.
On to glory.
Yeah, boo-boo!
That guy was hiding.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, I run out of mana fast here.
I need a nat mana.
That would be lovely.
Ow!
This guy has gotten 50 damage on me.
Wild.
But I don't care.
I have this and I have syphilis at home.
So do I really care about any of that?
I don't think so.
Hey-oh.
Fuck off.
No!
No.
Wait, what?
I guess there's unstable teleport- like polymorphism down there.
Change me.
Man, it must suck to be a Heezy Warrior because you don't have any UI at all.
You can't even see HP.
This is a massive drill.
Look at that.
They were drilling for gold.
Thank you.
I wonder if I can- Dude.
Dude, I know what to- We can activate this!
Fill it with oil?
Yo.
That's 100% what's happening here.
There's no way.
Whoops.
Go over here.
Oh, look at that.
No, no, no, wait.
It needs electricity, I think.
You see that electricity symbol here?
Do I have any?
I do have some- wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's try that.
Yeah!
Look!
What the fuck is working?!
I'm a goddamn genius!
How cool is that?!
I was expecting this thing to rotate, though, and dig, not plasma?
What?!
It's burning the oil when it's doing it.
That's the fuel for it.
Oh, that's awesome!
Here's the thing, though.
I should probably not stand in that, huh?
Exactly!
Didn't you just hear me?
Bad idea, bro.
And now it's off.
Awesome!
Wait, wait, my thing is not working, of course.
That was cool as hell!
Oh, this game makes me feel smart.
And that makes me happy.
Here we go.
Drink, drink, drink, drink.
Thanks.
So let me see where that actually dug.
Also, the whole drill bit disappeared.
Wow, it didn't do much, huh?
That was weird.
Now I need to just find more oil.
Oh, man.
Yep, this wand is not... There's a wand down here!
Aiming arc.
A projectile rotates towards the direction you're aiming.
Wait, as in a laser pointer?
Laser-guided missile-type deal?
Because that would be pretty cool.
I'm taking it, thank you.
And also that one.
Also, how is this wand?
It's bad.
Don't want that wand.
Thanks.
Let's try it.
Aiming arc.
Oh my god, I hate being slippery!
I hate cold crime scenes!
Now put this here.
I guess, okay.
If I had a rock, I could shoot it.
Aim with my mouse, and the rock would follow that, I guess.
Right?
Similar to the tow missiles on the APCs in Battlefield.
Or is it APVs?
Armored Personnel Vehicle, or Armored Personnel Carrier, something like that.
I don't like the chaotic polymorphine.
Bro, I dig even faster now!
I'm a digging god!
Not that I need it, because I can just go like, blubbly-bub!
And I'm between here and there, and nowhere.
I'm everywhere.
What can I say?
And now I go up, and I perform the oldest of the rituals in the land.
Called the Explore the West side of the Heezy Lab.
Or was it Heezy Base?
Either way.
Go!
Look at this, I can... I don't even care about walls.
Ah, here we go.
I'm at the left side now!
Uh, okay.
What's happening there?
Release it!
Drain that shit!
I have a feeling there may be a heart up there!
It's all freezing over, I don't like that.
Dang it.
Okay.
What's down this way?
Not much.
Whoop!
You scared me, man!
Hey, a heart!
Fuck yeah!
I actually forgot if this was the run where I left a... extra health.
Like 50% extra health in the first level or not.
Hold on, I can think about this.
So I went to... I went to coil... uh, coal pits, that's one.
Then I went to... snowy depths.
And then I went here.
Okay, yeah, this is not the run.
That was an earlier one.
But I will take some water.
I need to fill up more pheromone!
Or syphilis!
So I can't eat on the water, unfortunately, that's fine.
Drain the water.
Okay.
294 HP, ladies and gentlemen.
It is not bad.
What's happening here?
Oh ho ho!
Now we're talking!
I'm truly blessed on this day.
What's this?
Oh.
Movement is difficult.
Cause overeating.
Oh!
You don't say!
Aha!
So that's... what happens.
Okay, I ate too much blood.
I was a little too greedy.
I guess I'll just wait then.
Part of me wants to teleport into that acid, am I crazy?
Is that absolutely nuts?
I want to do it.
And then quickly out on the other side.
Should I do it?
Feels like a bad idea, right?
Yeah, let's not do it.
So that's... okay, so that's what the iron stomach perk does.
You can avoid getting these debuffs.
Right?
Because I've been wondering, what kind of debuffs are you talking about, dude?
Like... huh?
But I think I understand now.
Boink!
I need to see what's in there, dammit!
You know what?
It's fine.
I can drain it.
Oh yeah!
It gets turned into water!
Ah, okay, nice.
I see everything now.
Drain it all!
Oh, shit.
Eat this.
Oh wait, I shouldn't keep eating.
I have full stomach.
I'm fully satiated.
I do not need more food in my system.
That's what I keep telling myself in real life too all the time, you know?
But then somehow I always get this debuff in real life.
This is way too relatable.
Is it time to move on?
I think maybe it is.
Maybe pay a quick visit to Syphilis.
And also double check what spells I have up there.
Before I go.
I think that sounds reasonable.
Look at all that blood.
Oh wait, I can teleport.
I have to remember that.
Sweet.
Right, there was something here, but I don't care about that.
Is he here?
Syphilis?
My beloved?
No.
I was abandoned.
What?
Did he not like it here?
What's his problem?
It's quiet, it's peaceful.
There's spells to be had.
What's the issue here?
Motherfucker, I will remember that.
Okay, did I have any spells over here?
Doesn't look like it.
Okay.
Oh, I thought that was mana.
It's pheromone.
Okay, I think we may move on here.
Except...
Maybe I'll buy this.
Seems pretty cool.
Maybe I'll just for the lulz.
Maybe there's a use for that.
Who knows?
You never know.
I guess we can also technically leave the mountains now without angering anybody.
Which is pretty dope.
All right, I think we go.
Fuck yeah.
Let's see.
Triple...
This one.
Yes, sir.
Wait, why can't I... Oh, I have no more room.
Thanks.
Wait, what is that one?
Swapper.
Swapper?
The fuck is that?
Hold on.
Get rid of...
That one.
It was theorized that the source of qualia would be transferred.
But it turns out it was the whole body all along.
Say what now?
Wait a minute.
Oh, also.
Oh, that's enticing.
Oh!
Oh, dude.
We gotta take this one.
Hey!
Nice!
Awesome!
Okay, let's try this.
Hey.
Say what now?
I'm not sure what's happening there.
It looks like it swaps me and my enemy.
There's two people on this.
I was expecting this to go over here and I would go over there.
Maybe not.
That's weird.
Okay.
Now we have explosion immunity baby, right?
Yeah.
So that means...
Oh, what does that mean actually?
That means a lot, doesn't it?
Give me that.
Oh, I don't have any room.
Hmm...
Get rid of another one of these.
Home bringer.
What's this?
Large fireball.
Look at that.
Okay.
Now, what I really want is...
That one.
This is the big one.
Look at that.
It's such a difference.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, what did I just do?
There we go.
There it is, man.
There it fucking is.
That is just lovely.
What is this one?
Behind your back?
I think I had that one before.
I couldn't quite understand it.
Whatever.
I'm going to leave that here for now.
I kind of want to try...
That's going to be a way to do something even more crazy here.
Like, I have...
Ah, man, I want the spark bolt right now.
Why didn't I keep it?
Massive.
Oh, wait a minute.
What if I do this now?
After the reduced...
Spread plus 40?
Yo!
Oh, no, never mind.
Never mind.
What I really need is multiple triplicate bolts now.
That would be sick.
That would be disgusting.
Unfortunately, I don't have it.
Let's just put this here for now.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
That's it, baby.
And we have this and we have that.
Ah, this one, though.
Sure.
We could keep some of the stuff here.
Like, one of these can stay here.
Maybe the chunk of soil stays here.
Stays here.
This one.
Yeah.
That seems good.
All right, man.
We're back.
Back in the jungle.
Digging blast!
I enjoy some digging blast.
I shall take it.
And I shall put the digging blast...
on my digging wand.
I mean, yeah, it's pretty good, I guess.
0.1, 0.45.
Yep.
Man, I want melee immunity here.
Fuck the spiders.
The spiders can really go fuck themselves.
Hopefully I'm able to actually kill them this time.
Sometimes they don't take any damage and I don't understand why.
Barren soil.
What a weird name for a baron.
Soil.
I can drink this.
Blood.
Because I am not satiated anymore.
My stomach is empty.
Ready to consume.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
No, thanks.
Aha!
Ouch.
Man, what if I...
Never mind.
Drink blood.
And I don't think I'm afraid of the gods anymore.
Like, I have enough power now to not be afraid of them, I think.
So if I were to anger them by going back, I think we're fine.
Fuck, yeah.
Love having an MG42.
No!
That was a friendo!
Fuck me, I didn't realize they were in here.
Damn it!
Well, now I know to keep an eye out.
What the hell is that?
Reduced lifetime.
Oh.
Hold on, when is that good?
When is that a good thing?
Maybe with the death cross or whatever, you know, the one that takes a while to activate?
That could be a nice thing to do.
Oh, it actually also reduces cast delay.
Hey, that's not... that's not bad.
I shall take it.
These ones, though, do I like it?
I don't know.
No, I don't think I like it.
Maybe I'll take one of them just to have.
And then replace it with...
that one.
I don't really want those.
Switch it back.
Okay, here we are.
Yikes!
Oh, man.
That is nasty.
It's like they were all acting together as one organism.
Fucked up, that is.
Holy crap.
And I have a powerful wand.
And I need to eat more, but I think there's poison in between this.
I need to be careful here when I eat.
Half of it is... is that not... no, that's slime, okay.
Slime is also bad to eat, I guess.
Good.
Get rid of that one.
Also, we got to go visit the Dragon Cave.
Say hi to our old buddy.
Wand up there.
Oh.
Wow, we got a mine off before he died.
So did that guy.
Go collect his money.
Drink his blood.
And cause a flood.
Yeah!
Love flooding things.
Chaos magic!
Makes a projectile launch a random spell out of a limited selection.
When it hits something.
How about no?
But you know what?
That wand is actually kind of dope.
Hello?
Like, how is that wand not sick?
That wand is...
Honestly.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Is that enough?
No, we need this, I think.
It's better.
The only issue is, we don't have enough...
We don't have enough slots if we find some mana later on.
You know, that's like the issue here.
That's bad.
That's really bad.
Do we need this?
Yeah, we kind of need it.
At least for now.
So let's put it back up here.
No!
I had twitchy fingers.
Let's be careful, let's not die in some stupid way right now.
That would be hilariously bad.
Don't do it.
I kind of want to keep these.
They seem kind of crazy good.
Maybe also...
Get rid of that one.
Take another one.
No, only one of these, because if I ever want to fire these, it's because I have unlimited spells.
Actually, this one is better than...
Why don't I just do this?
And get rid of that one instead.
This is now my...
Is it better?
Hold on.
Why is it slower?
.10, .45?
Yeah?
What?
Wait, is this one I threw away?
Oh, .07.
Is that really the only difference?
That's crazy.
What?
I mean, I guess it is kind of a big difference.
If you think about it.
Hold on, what if I were to do...
That?
Oh, I wish I had the board right now.
So it's gonna cast this one.
Oh, I need to do this.
Yeah!
Okay, listen, this is how it works.
It cast chainsaw, okay?
And chainsaw reduces recharge time.
Then I cast a double spell, which casts two spells.
So this one, what's the next spell?
Another chainsaw.
So what's happening is...
This effect, this status effect of the chainsaw is being applied twice.
Hahaha!
Fuck yeah!
And now we're gonna take this and put it here.
Okay, go up here.
I feel so happy about that because usually when I use the chainsaw, you know, it's...
I just play around with it until it works.
But there I actually had a plan, I was like, this makes sense to switch it around there because of that.
And it worked because of that.
I think I'm finally maybe starting to understand the chainsaw.
Oh my god, look at the digging!
We're unstoppable.
Except dense rock.
Dense rock is kind of what stops us.
Other than that, we're unstoppable.
Look, I got...
Okay, we need something that can dig.
We need a proper digger.
A digging machine.
That's what we need.
Oh, hello there!
Quadruple spell!
Thank you!
I will take it.
What's that?
Whoa!
Plasma beam.
Does that dig?
Are we in digging territory?
Whoa!
Why is it angled like... Okay, hold on.
I thought at least it would be like a cross and not like a fucking X.
God damn it.
Whatever.
Put this bag up here and replace...
I don't even know.
I don't even know like that one.
Don't want it!
What's this?
We can encourage melee.
Target hit by a projectile takes 25% extra melee damage for a time.
Eh, sure.
Why not?
We can play with that, I guess.
Maybe I don't like this accelerating shot.
Maybe I hate it, actually.
Point... Oh wait, this is actually a decent want, no?
Wait a minute.
Yeah!
That's...
That's a decent want, right there.
I kind of want to get rid of this.
I don't like the quantum split.
That's way better.
And .07.
Oh, lolololololololo!
Did we make it even better somehow?
Oh my gosh!
Hold on, is it actually better?
I think it's about equal.
But the castile is much lower.
Whatever.
I mean, I'm going to keep this wand.
This is a good wand.
It's a good wand.
Yep.
In fact, let's take these with me then, because I can actually put them...
I can actually use these wands as storage.
I just need to be careful not to put anything scary on them.
Digging is fine.
Something that won't hurt me if I accidentally use it, you know what I mean?
Maybe that one, and maybe that one.
Sure, just storage wand.
Teleport, damage, digging, storage.
Cool!
Let's go.
The tracking cave I have arrived!
It's time.
But I need to heal.
I've got to find some blood first.
I found some blood.
Got to find more blood.
Sirs, please die.
Drink.
Man, this is not enough blood.
I need more blood.
This blood makes me unhappy.
Ah, hold on.
We have got a wand as well.
What's going on here?
Oh wait, I'm eating something in between there.
That's not good for me, I don't think.
The fuck is that?
Two-way fireball thrower?
Jesus.
No, thank you.
That's a bit too crazy for me.
Okay.
I think it's time for the tracking cave.
And we have to remember, the way to spawn them is to go next to it when I have dug it.
I'm still kind of scared of this guy.
Oh God.
Oh, I don't like this.
Wait, I used the wrong wand there.
Oh!
That is so scary.
Come here, come here.
Holy shit.
Oh, sick.
Okay, what do we got?
That is a big wand.
Yo, what the hell?
That's a really good wand, I think.
Put this stuff here...
and grab that.
There we go.
Let's see this.
What is that?
Chaotic transmutation.
Transmutes various liquids and powder substances within a projectile's range into something else?
Whoa, that sounds cool!
Fuck yeah!
That sounds pretty awesome!
Uh...
I don't want any of these.
Yo, I have never seen this many slots on a wand, I don't think.
Never seen this.
I mean, this is the ideal storage wand, I guess, for now.
Unless, hold on...
.20 point...
Dude, this is...
This is nuts.
Why is it not as fast?
Recharge?
Ah, recharge is too high.
I see.
But I could fix that with this.
Let me just double check my theory here.
If I put this here, this should be completely fine now.
Look how much it shoots...
compared to the other one.
But now I don't have the speed digging.
So I will put this back up here, actually, for now.
And this will be a storage wand.
Put all
of this on here.
This one...
sounds really... Oh, there's only eight uses of it, too!
Wow!
Interesting.
Okay.
Sure.
Nothing that can kill me.
That's fine.
There we go.
Now, what is that?
Plasma beam orbit.
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No way.
Did I just discover digging?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Use...
Actually, use one of these.
Wait, what?
Wait, a hundred man... Oh, wait, we don't have enough mana.
I think.
129.
This should...
Oh, yeah, it only activates at the first shot.
And then the next ones, they don't have any.
Ah, it doesn't dig, though.
But maybe you can make it crazy.
If you actually have enough mana and you can sustain it in brrrr, you know?
I'm gonna keep it.
Could be really cool.
But for now, I go with that.
Very cool.
Let's go.
What's going on in here?
Ah, I don't want to tangle with that.
Also, I'm starting to get a little too quick.
I just slowed down a bit here.
The game just came to a crawl.
Did you see that?
That was weird.
Hopefully nothing's gonna crash again.
I am worried.
Also, I'm slimy.
Go up here.
I need to eat more blood.
What's happening?
Ah, it's you, sir.
You, sir.
Me, sir?
You want a shave?
I shall give you one.
Friend!
No, no, no, no, no, come here, come here.
Oh, no, he's stuck!
You're free.
Yes!
Friend!
This is awesome.
Huh?
Dude, I just had the craziest idea.
Remember how I tried to keep Syphilis in my home?
I just thought of a use for the...
Homebringer bolt.
Okay, watch this.
Let's say...
Okay.
Dude.
Oh, hold on, there's a spider here?
Oh, no!
Syphilis!
Oh, I'm so sorry, fuck, well...
Anyway, I couldn't do what I'm about to tell you anyway.
But I'm gonna tell you now.
Listen.
Long distance cast, okay?
With a...
Yeah, I guess, yeah, just long... Dude, this, watch.
Basically this.
You do this?
Hold on.
You get the idea?
I make a hole inside somewhere, right?
Okay, I made a nice hole.
Then I long distance cast teleport in there.
Then I make a long distance cast Homebringer.
Bring him in there.
Then I fill the little room with...
Fuck, what's it called?
Pheromone, right?
I long distance teleport myself out.
Bam!
He's always in there.
He's always my friend.
Whenever I want to heal, boom!
Long distance cast inside of there.
Huh?
What do you say to that?
That's fucking genius.
Oh, yeah.
Eh, I'm so slow now.
Oh, look, I'm fully slimed up.
Let's blood myself up instead, that's better.
Uh, that's peace.
Okay, we're fine.
Aiming arc.
Why do I find so many good wands?
I guess it's because I'm in the jungle and there's just better wands here.
But I just feel like I find so many good ones right now.
There was another one here.
Oh, yeah, I have explosion immunity.
Also, the game is slowing down to a crawl again.
I swear it's not the slime.
It's something about the jungle.
My computer can't fucking handle this place.
This place is nuts.
Let's go over here.
Oh!
Wait, did I already discover this?
I did, okay.
Oh, hello.
What's over there?
Nothing.
Okay, no wand.
Nothing at all.
Okay, portal there.
I kinda wanna anger the gods.
Is that crazy?
Mostly because I wanna get some payback on these fuckers.
They're killing me last time.
The gods think they're above me?
Right.
Not today, sucker.
I am the man who shall take on the gods.
Come at me, bro.
I will fuck you up.
Aha!
Once again, the man finds more HP.
And the man is stronger for it.
And man finds more.
The man is unstoppable.
He cannot be stopped.
The gods are crying.
Okay, I need to slow down here.
I'm going a little too fast.
Also, blood me up.
I've been here.
I need to drink this blood.
Am I crazy or am I starting to drink more blood and get diminishing returns on the healing?
It feels like I need more blood to heal the same amount now as it did early on.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Maybe there's something there, maybe not.
Who knows?
Kick this box!
Oh, that's the entrance.
Very neat.
Is it, though?
Aha!
Oh my god.
All right.
I don't want that.
Hey, guys.
Oh, this is a feast for a vampire.
And I am a vampire.
Drink it up.
This is my own little healing chamber now.
There we go.
Vampirism, man.
Oh my god.
It has healed me so much.
What a perk.
Incredible.
Oh, should we get high?
Aha!
Now we're talking, dude.
More of these.
What's this one again?
Cast three spells.
Ahead, above, and below the caster.
Hey, you.
So I'm going to do this now.
And then I'm going to do this.
And then I'm going to add a quadruple.
Oh, I go way quicker.
Yeah.
Maybe we do that and just add a triple, huh?
I don't even have a triple.
Maybe that's too much.
Maybe there's a thing that's too much.
I will save this for later.
Also, my wand is wrong.
Switch it back for my digging.
Stick around.
I have a lot of HP.
There's a guide on there.
Who was he shooting at?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Blade safe, blade safe.
There's a bomb.
Where are you?
Is he all the way up here?
He was!
Drink.
You know what?
I kind of don't want to get high.
And the reason is...
It's going so well.
I can imagine getting high and...
Suddenly, blood is now lava.
And vampirism is no more and my life is a joke.
So, you know, let's not risk it.
We're not getting high this time.
Nope.
We're staying sober for this one, boys.
What's going on there?
Oh, pheromone!
I need that.
I actually need that.
Drains!
Wait, what's this?
Oh, it's flammable gas!
Why does it look like that?
Oh, and there's health in there too.
Incredible.
Wait, I can't breathe in here though.
Okay, I got it.
Why is the music like this?
We got to dig.
Does that turn it on?
It doesn't.
Okay.
Sweet.
Now we got to eat more blood.
Got to stay topped off, you know.
This is one of the tenets we're going to adopt in this run.
Always be topped off on HP.
Whenever possible, of course.
Who's that?
I'm scared of these mages, by the way.
Where did he go?
Whoa!
No, he's there.
He's there.
Are you still there, sir?
He's still there.
I think he died.
He did not die.
He teleported me.
This is what I hate about these guys.
They do some unpredictable shit.
I'm so scared of them.
You never know what to expect, you know?
Wait, I thought you were dead.
Hey, you there.
I see you.
There's also a spot.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, man, the game is crawling along.
Is it just me?
Am I just slow?
I mean, I am slow, but hold on.
Get bloodied?
Get completely bloodied.
Okay, maybe it was just me.
I should be digging everywhere.
Like, I can basically walk through Earth.
It sounds nuts, but it's true.
Hello, what's up, guys?
Please get away from me.
Hello?
Why will this not explode?
What?
I'm scared.
What else we got?
I am cleaning this place of hearts.
And I love it.
Kill them all.
I actually don't do a lot of damage to these guys for some reason.
Like, they're very resistant to damage.
Little baby spiders, they are crazy.
Okay, I don't think I want timers.
That doesn't please me.
He's my friend.
Haha, just look at his digging.
It's insane.
Finally!
That's what we've been waiting for, baby.
Wait a minute, what was that?
Fireball orbit.
Yeah, no thanks.
Aww, yeah!
Haha!
Watch, we can make it even more crazy now.
It runs out, but I think it's much more powerful now.
Right, it shoots twice the amount.
It's double the damage pretty much now.
Does a man even need double the damage?
That is the question, isn't it?
Probably not.
But, uh, fuck it.
I enjoy the double damage.
I think the game is definitely slowing down.
Look at how the physics, everything is moving slowly.
It's not just me.
I need to... Honestly, I need to get a new CPU.
I have a really old one.
It's pretty much the bottleneck of my system.
And this game is definitely limited by the CPU, I can tell you that.
I also really want to get that CPU before I play something like Cyberpunk, because it's apparently super demanding.
Aww, the game is so slow.
Oh, man.
Guys, I'm gonna save and quit, just so it has a save point.
In case everything gets corrupted again.
I'm scared of that suddenly crashing and everything is fucked again.
That scarred me for life, man.
Oh, it's... Oh, we're back.
Much faster now.
Oh, we've got one of those guys.
The lightning guys.
Nothing else up here?
Ah, there you are.
Blow him out of... Fucking blow him up to bits.
Here we go.
I'm basically like a worm.
Look at these tunnels.
This is how a worm digs.
I have become the worm.
It's amazing.
This is way too much fun.
Are you kidding me, man?
This is just great.
Fuck off.
We were just staring at each other for a little while there.
And I was frozen in place.
That's a spider.
I see you there.
Oh, man.
The game is slowing down again.
It's always jungle.
I think when I move on from jungle, it's going to be okay again.
Ah, trash your chests.
Ah, come on.
I don't need money.
Or do I?
I don't think I do.
Even the small spiders take a lot of damage now after I...
added an extra triplicate.
What's happening down here?
Very nice.
I would love to find that extra HP now.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I missed it.
Yeah, definitely not.
Then I don't go in there at all.
Hate that place.
It's so hard to play when the game is so slow.
Nothing is like muscle movement at all, you know?
I've gotten used to one speed and now I can't.
Do it probably.
What is that?
Huh?
This is absolute chaos.
Oh no.
Oh my god, the game is so slow.
Did that spider die?
Fantastic.
No, it didn't.
Or maybe that's another one.
Oh no.
Wait.
Did you see that?
Is he healing?
Look at the...
There were healing symbols on him, I swear.
Okay, I can't kill him for some reason.
So we're leaving.
You know?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not dealing with that.
We're leaving this place.
Fuck that shit.
No.
Surprise.
Oops.
Drink the blood.
Oh yeah, delicious blood.
There we go.
We could leave.
Wouldn't be a terrible idea.
Actually it would.
Because we're not done exploring.
And there's no reason to leave.
But it is in fact a terrible idea.
But I need to slow down still.
This is the killer.
When I don't slow down.
I take damage from this.
Am I eating something I shouldn't?
I'm eating fire, that's bad.
That's better.
That's another portal.
Or it was a portal and then a spider duck down here.
Look.
Oh no.
I'm sorry.
No.
God damn it.
I mean I can kill them, right?
Tell me I can kill them.
I need to have a... okay.
Let's have a backup in case this doesn't do anything for some reason.
I can hot swap the triplicate with...
In fact, let's get rid of one of these so we have infinite.
I don't even know.
What do we know kills them?
A rock.
I don't know.
Nah, put it back, that's fine.
Nah, we're gonna kill them, we're gonna kill them.
It's no problem.
He's gonna die, man.
He's gonna fucking die.
Right?
No problem.
There's no way we're gonna...
Wait, am I tripping?
I'm not tripping.
What's that?
Teleportation?
No thanks.
What is that?
Auto aim.
How is that different from homing though?
I guess I want to find out.
Let's keep it.
I need to find out what the hell's going on there.
Another portal.
Oh, you know what?
Let's grab some worm blood.
We have pheromones, so it's fine.
Hell yeah.
If we ever go back to the...
I mean, we are gonna go back.
When we go back to the dark cave...
We're gonna have worm blood.
Yeah!
Get it.
I feel like I should go through.
Yeah, let's go through.
I've explored most of this place.
Hey, you.
The hell you think you're doing?
Oh wait, we gotta be prepared.
He's here.
Let's get ready.
Hold on, in case...
I'm gonna try this in case it doesn't work, okay?
We're gonna switch this out.
Hot swap.
Also, I'm gonna take this away for now.
Just so I can dodge more easily.
Sir?
Okay!
It's no problem!
He's dead!
He died, bitch!
Yup!
Easy peasy.
Lemon squeezy.
Alright, that's no issue.
Intense concentrated light.
Let's see what the perks are.
What the hell is that one?
Oh, the permanent shield!
I think I want that.
Thanks.
Get rid of all this fucking...
Bone dust or whatever that is.
I like having this permanent shield.
It's actually really nice.
Okay!
Now this one.
Intense concentrated light.
It's infinite...
Ooh, 125 damage.
Oh, but it adds a shit ton of castellae!
Wow!
Let's try it, though.
What?
I hurt myself.
Oh, I'm scared of this now.
Why is that doing that?
Oh, a spectral wand is summoned!
That casts a huge...
Oh, that's weird.
Wait, what?
So hold on, long distance on that, or what?
Oh!
Oh, wait a minute!
Have I not seen that before?
One of the bosses did that shit to me.
Right?
I remember that effect.
Dude, that is kind of crazy.
I mean, I like it.
Could be a lot of damage.
But, hold on.
What was this one again?
Facing arc.
Can I read the description of this without having to...
Buy it, by the way?
Is that even a thing?
I don't think you can.
Ah, whatever.
I'm buying it.
Makes the projectile fly much slower, but teleports short distances over its flight.
Right.
It reduces cast-a-lay?
That's something.
Is that something I want?
Let's see how that looks.
What?
Is there any difference there?
I'm honestly not quite sure.
I mean, much slower.
You almost can't feel it, right, because I have the speed up and everything?
And it's a very fast projectile to begin with.
I even have this now.
I could put this somewhere to make something even crazier.
Actually, I could put it down here now.
This could be my new wand.
Because the issue I had was recharge, right?
And we don't suffer from that anymore.
Yeah.
Maybe get rid of this one.
I don't like that.
And maybe also get rid of...
I don't know.
Maybe the Swapper.
Yeah.
Do that now.
So watch this.
Kind of slow, right?
But now...
This doesn't matter where.
Now we're shooting fast.
And the reason this is better is because now we have more options for later.
We can do all kinds of crazy shit with this wand.
Is this teleporting short distances?
I can't tell.
Say what?
Oh, wait.
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Let's try that.
Huh.
Weird.
I can't tell the teleportation here.
Maybe I need something so I can see it more easily.
Like an energy orb.
Maybe I can see that stuff.
Or maybe remove the speed up just for this so I can see.
Put this in.
Oh, yeah, it does.
You see that?
Dup, dup, dup, dup.
Oh, you know what?
That's good for though.
Oh, I know what it's useful for.
Some bosses, you have to get through a shield.
Or enemy slash bosses, they have a shield, right?
And then you absorb those layers before you get in.
This way you can penetrate the shield.
And hit them directly.
Oh...
That's big.
That's actually big.
Maybe I'll roll with that.
I can hot swap it later if I need to, right?
It's fine.
This one down here I can even do...
Oh, that one's already fast AF, boy.
Let's do something like that.
I can even put stuff like this on it, I guess.
We have the means to do that now.
Reduce the lifetime?
Let's try that.
Is the lifetime actually reduced?
I don't know.
Maybe it is.
Hard to say.
Yeah.
Wait, I just had an idea.
I had an idea.
Wait a second.
What if I...
Hold on, I just had an idea.
It shoots that.
This is a projectile.
But that projectile could have a modifier.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Did that actually do anything?
Baby!
Okay, remember when I said before down here that I was using the chainsaw twice?
I'm doing the same thing with the mana, baby.
Yeah!
And you know what?
It makes sense too!
That's freaking awesome!
Oh yeah, baby.
That is... Hold on, what else am I missing out?
Can I double the damage then?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
Hold on, hold your horses.
400 something.
Let me...
No, that's way worse.
Wait, is it?
I'm not sure.
Hold on.
Oh wait, that's...
Why is that suddenly so good?
Modifier, modifier, modifier.
It shouldn't matter which direction this is.
So wait.
Wait, is it...
Oh.
Hold on.
I think I do more damage without the phasing arc, because it's much faster projectile.
But the phasing arc will, I think, penetrate the shields of certain enemies really well.
That's why I choose to have this in here.
I think that's good for now.
That's pretty good.
So hold on, if I do this, and then put this one there...
Oh yeah, it definitely increases.
And look how much I can spam it now.
Wild stuff.
Oh, wow!
Instead of 600, we're in the 2000s now, baby.
And so this is something you wouldn't be able to tell without having this...
Target dummy, I guess you could say.
Right?
Wild.
Very cool.
Oh, man.
Leon.
Actually, I want to buy this and throw this one out instead.
Watch this one again.
Fly downwards.
Boo!
I don't want that.
Let's go.
Let's fucking go.
Is everything in set?
It's not set.
Hold on.
Where's my teleporter?
There it is.
All right, baby.
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe you should try going up now.
I anger the gods anyway, right?
So it doesn't fucking matter now.
I feel like I'm strong enough.
I'm strong enough to go have another visit to the dentist.
The chiropractor.
The guy with the spells.
Oh, wait, can I...
Oh, look at this.
I don't need to be able to dig here.
Oh, wait, I need to dig.
I mean, right, not right here, but further on, I need to dig.
I don't have any digging.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Digging, digging, digging.
I actually have no way of...
Shit.
Okay.
I'm going to move on right now.
Just so I can find something to dig with.
I mean, maybe plasma cutter or a black hole, whatever.
I just need something.
And when I find it, I can go back.
That's the plan.
So, let's go.
We have arrived in the vault.
Oh, man, that is a slow projectile now, isn't it?
Maybe I'll hot swap this out or hot swap it in when I need it.
For now, I'm going to keep it like that.
Hey, what's up, guys?
Oh, that's lovely.
That is lovely.
Ah, my shield is doing work already.
Lovely stuff.
Let's keep going.
Look, you see these?
These are the ones that have the shield.
But I guess with a wand as fast as this, in those cases, it doesn't matter.
Because I break the shield so quick.
And the next projectile in the sequence is already going to hit it, right?
Before the shield comes back online.
But watch this.
It's hot swap time, baby.
Yo, why does that look like that?
What?
Oh, is it because reduce spread comes before that?
That's why.
That looks so fucked.
Hey, guys.
How's it going in there?
I'm just cleaning up here.
Everything dies.
Amazing.
Oh, wait.
I can't even dig through that, but I can teleport through it.
Funny.
Way too much oil here for my taste.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, this is bad.
It's getting a little too chaotic.
I got to come down here.
Maybe the enemies need to come down as well.
This is getting a little nuts.
It's not just me, okay?
They started it.
Give me some blood here, please.
I guess there's not a lot of organic enemies here.
That guy's organic.
Eat the organic guy.
Oh, I ate some oil.
Oh, there we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
We're eating good tonight.
I may eat a couple extra things here, but that's fine.
Oh, shit.
Can we get rid of this fire, please?
Nah, I'm taking more damage than healing right now.
I need to wait for this fire to go away.
Dammit!
Let me drink over here.
That's what I'm talking about.
This is the spot.
Oh, yeah.
Fill me up, baby.
Scoop it up into my belly.
Make me whole again.
Oh, look at this fool.
Jesus.
What a mess.
Ambrosia!
No!
That guy was briefly protected by Ambrosia.
Until he wasn't.
And then he died.
I'm protected now.
Just by standing in it.
We could get high, but I'm not gonna.
We're staying sober, remember?
I'm stuck.
Stupid frogs.
More Ambrosia.
I gotta find an empty bottle.
Or empty one of the ones I have.
Kinda want to keep the pheromone, though.
For the healing.
Maybe it's better to...
I could throw away this tablet and find another bottle.
That's probably the best way.
The tablet is not that useful anymore.
It's actually a really good early game.
But like this?
Nah, not anymore.
We're fine.
Invisiblium.
Wait, why is my screen all...
Oh, I'm tripping.
That's why.
Hey!
Cool.
Come on, show me a digging wand, man.
Plasma cutter, please.
Show thyself to me.
At least I can dig through this.
That's something.
Aha!
But can I get in there, though?
Wait, I can.
So cool.
But scary, too, you know?
Rotate towards foes.
Yo, that wand is nuts.
That's a crazy good wand, man.
Wow.
One, two, three, four, six, seven slots.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Damn!
That is a good wand.
I could switch it out with that, I guess.
Why wouldn't I?
It's just better in every way.
I'm doing it.
There.
Get out of here.
Then we go... Wait, what?
Oh, yeah, right.
There's a bunch of shit on it.
Here.
There.
Beautiful.
There's a healthy baby wand.
Perfect in every way.
What is that?
Oh, it had like a red symbol on it.
Made me curious.
You see that?
He didn't die.
The shield is still doing something there.
Oh, that guy's stuck in there, huh?
But watch, we can deal with that.
Hot swap time.
Amazing.
What's up with all this oil?
Why was there so much oil?
All that oil came from that little crab?
That's wild.
Okay, this is looking pretty... What is that?
Is that just the background?
Oh, yeah, it is.
I thought there was some kind of liquid.
Ah, sure.
Water me?
I need to find some blood here.
Oh, god.
Too much fire.
Would love fire resistance in here.
Damn.
Don't go in there.
Let's go this way.
The hell, who was he?
He had a cape on and shit.
Seemed important.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I need blood.
A lot of it.
This'll do.
So this thing releases freezing vapor, and this thing releases fire.
You see that?
I feel like that's curious.
There we go.
That's too much fun.
Oh, god.
A wand up there.
This could be a lucky day.
In fact, there's all this blood, too.
That makes me happy.
Jesus Christ, this is a mess.
This is acceleration.
Okay.
I thought it was teleportation for a second.
Oh, my goodness.
Jesus Christ!
What's happening here?
Are we okay?
Drink the blood, man.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, it comes to fire again.
Something is fireworking.
Let's just calm down a bit.
Teleport.
Nah.
Not exactly what I was looking for.
Oh, no, I'm taking... I'm trying to drink the fucking blood.
Ah, most of the blood is gone now.
Shit!
I need pure blood.
Not this muggler blood.
Or whatever they call it in Harry Potter.
Because I'm a wizard, get it?
I can't drink.
Here we go.
Set me on fire, I don't care.
Ah, man, what is happening?
How do I take out the damn fire on the blood?
It's so weird.
Ah, here comes the oil.
It's gonna make it worse.
That's so annoying.
I wish I had a straw.
I would just go...
No, put the straw in the blood there and just slurp it up.
That's what I need, man.
Ah, that thing's gonna explode, no?
Oh, yeah, that thing explodes.
Quite a big explosion, too.
Come on, oil!
Burn!
What if I water it a little bit?
Just a bit.
Hey, that's actually not bad.
Except I'm out of water.
Here we go!
I don't care.
There must be oil in there somewhere.
Whatever.
Let's go find some more blood.
Scary stuff.
And that guy just spawns oil.
Left and right.
The most oily guy ever.
The crab.
The mechanical crab.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I don't have any water.
Oh, no.
I am slowly losing all of my HP here.
Didn't I have some blood somewhere?
Up here?
Maybe here?
Is that berserkium?
It is, okay.
I can drink that, I think.
Oh, yeah, that's totally fine.
Yeah, there we go.
I'm like an addict on the lookout for my next fix here.
Wait, I'm tripping.
Oh, no, I accidentally ate some mushrooms.
There goes our pin.
The three-month pin.
And the drug's anonymous.
I mean, since we're starting now, we can just go all the way, right?
May as well eat all the mushrooms now.
I have some blood here.
But molten metal as well.
I don't think I want to eat that.
Shit.
And still no proper digging wand found.
That's kind of a...
I really need that.
Are you there?
Oh, no.
Water, water, water, water.
Oh, thank God.
I need some water immediately.
I am draining HP here.
Bleeding.
Oh, man.
Everything hurts me when I drink.
Why?
It's just blood.
Ah, here we go.
Water.
Uh, get rid of that.
Fill up the bottle.
Oh, yeah.
No, I don't want your slime in here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How fucking dare you.
There we go.
Full on water.
That's something, at least.
That is something.
Okay, I feel better now.
Now.
Widely and slowly.
Wow.
He shoots missiles.
What is that right there?
There's a chest.
Gold.
Nice.
Why did I just take damage from?
Whoa.
Did you see that?
Is that you, sir?
What the fuck is that?
Interesting spell there.
Who's doing that?
You need... I need to find a friendo.
Because I have a lot of pheromone.
Maybe there's friendos down here.
Bunch of blood here I can drink.
Ah, shit.
Some of this is toxic shit.
Oh, no.
Oh, there's a lot of blood here, though.
This is good, this is good.
Stand here and eat.
It's going to take a while.
And I'm going to need a lot of blood.
But it works.
It works.
Very nice.
Okay.
Two hundred something.
It's crazy how all that blood physically fits inside my body.
I've been eating a lot.
Drink this blood as well.
All of it.
Damn, I am one thirsty vampire.
Phew.
That was neat.
Anyone else come here?
There we go.
Come on.
Get rid of that one.
All the explosives can go away.
The hell is that?
Looks like a slime bunny.
That's disturbing to me.
I don't enjoy the slime bunny.
We've got some blood there, but it's... ooh.
Giant fire bolt.
I don't remember if this one digs through dense rock.
Maybe it does.
Maybe not.
I'm not sure.
Wait, is this guy healing?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Why is he not a friend?
Why are you not a friend?
Why are you no friend?
Come on.
Maybe because he's a mechanical and I try to put pheromone on him, which is like something you do with animals.
That's probably what's going on there.
But man, I just saw an opportunity.
And I'm so sad it didn't work.
But actually, hold on.
I have an idea.
Come up here.
Where'd he go?
Mr. Healer Man.
Oh, never mind.
I was going to try and stand in between the enemy and the Healer Man and get hit by the healing if he were to heal his friend.
And with my shield on, maybe I would have repelled whatever the actual enemy would do to me, you know?
What the fuck?
A bunch of bomb cards.
I wonder if this will dig.
Let's actually test that.
Oh, but this always casts horizontal barrier.
I say no to that.
That shit scares the crap out of me.
No thanks.
And we've got another wand.
Glue ball.
Nah.
Not feeling any of that.
Gotta be honest there.
Don't just shoot that purple shit at me.
Anyone else?
Want some?
Come into range.
You there.
Everyone there.
Let's go drink some blood.
And turn this into water.
Am I drinking toxic shit?
Wrap some of the water first.
Okay.
Stand here.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
What?
What just happened?
There was a cloud over me.
I'm scared.
What's happening?
Uh...
Am I not allowed to drink this blood, oh gods above?
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
Uh...
Okay.
Huh?
What have I done?
Thank you.
Turn this into water.
Mix it up good.
Get rid of the fire.
Gotta filter your blood before you drink it, people.
Filter your blood and wash your bread.
The important things in life.
What's happening here?
Why is there a cloud on me?
I'm scared.
I'm scared I'm gonna suddenly be electrocuted.
Quickly drink the blood.
Drink it all.
Slurp it up.
Slurpy, slurpy.
Mmm.
Whoop.
Eh?
Is there an enemy nearby casting something on me?
That's the only theory I have.
This is my new strategy.
I go to a new place and I just sit in one spot.
And I shoot everything that moves into range.
The fuck is that?
Oh no.
I do no damage to him.
Wait, this is the time.
Try this.
Doesn't work.
Shit.
It does work!
Oh!
He doesn't die though.
I guess he has a lot of HP.
Holy shit.
Come here.
Sir?
Oh my god, that's so scary looking.
Where did he go?
Man, he's just off somewhere.
You know, maybe that's okay.
He can go dig around.
Make holes for me.
But wait a minute, if he came from up above...
No, no, no.
He still needs to go all the way up to the...
snowy depths at least.
If I have to get anything out of that.
Is that molten?
No, that's... yeah, molten metal is right there.
That's scary.
The game is lagging again.
I think it has something to do with the spiders.
Because it lagged in the jungle.
And the spiders were there.
I think when the spiders are digging, the game lags.
That's my theory.
I think it's really related to that.
It's gotta be...
Like, I feel it instantly.
I'm definitely drinking something bad there.
Pure blood right here.
That's nice.
That's what we want to see.
What?
I'm still taking damage.
Why am I taking damage?
I hate it, man.
Oh...
Wait!
That is connected.
I gotta update the map with that.
The luki layer connects the vault to the jungle.
Right?
Get rid of the oil, please.
But honestly, I'm kind of scared to open the map right now.
I have PTSD after that time.
I switched scenes.
The game crashed.
And I had to reload, save or whatever, and it corrupted my world.
Maybe... Oh god.
Maybe I will do that stuff...
After I click save and exit.
And then I'll do it.
Kill that... Oh my god, the game is so slow, it's wild.
Lots of blood here, though.
That's a potential healing.
Oh yeah, I'm getting good healing here.
And it's raining on me, too.
This is a fucking Dracula's dream.
I'm having a blood shower and everything.
Oh, lovely.
Okay, the fire is approaching me now.
Lovely.
Where's all this blood come from?
What's dripping?
What?
A huge collection of blood up there, apparently.
But I don't mind.
This is the ultimate blood shower.
I love it.
Oh yeah.
Drink it up.
Endless supply of blood here.
Oh yeah, almost full HP.
This is awesome.
This is definitely awesome.
Nice.
So where did all that blood come from here, huh?
Huh, cool.
That's pretty neat.
Wand!
Hey!
Damage plus.
Hook bolt.
I don't really want that, I don't think.
This could actually be a nice wand for this, specifically.
You know?
I may actually do it.
Hold on.
Let me grab this.
Oh, wait a minute.
Kill that guy.
Get rid of all this.
Quickly scan area, no enemies, good.
If I can stack this, imagine.
Oh wait, this casts two spells per.
That's okay, hold on, maybe that'll work too.
I need to keep an eye out here.
I have just about enough space here.
So if this casts two spells per,
it's kind of slow right now.
Faster.
But I guess I need to see the damage on it.
Oh, but wait a minute.
This damage right here.
That's being applied at the start.
It's going to apply to the chainsaw and not actually...
Hold on.
Why is there such dramatic music?
Okay, I think we're fine.
I think this damage plus is applying to the chainsaw and not actually the triplicate bolt.
So what if I were to...
put this inside of here such that this modifier is adding with along the other modifiers everything to this.
I'm not sure.
Wait a minute.
0.02, 0.25.
0.02.
Why is this one...
It's something about the two spells per cast that's messing with me here.
So it's going to do two spells, which means it's going to cast this one and another one.
So maybe the simple answer here is to simply do that.
Yeah, maybe.
No.
So it's going to cast modifier, modifier, modifier, modifier, modifier.
First spell, but that first spell contains four spells.
And one of those spells is a double spell.
So that's these... Okay, so hold on.
There's already an issue here I see.
So this is the first spell and this next spell is after, so this is fine.
So now we can...
do... wait a minute, one, two...
No, no, no, no, wait a minute.
What if I just remove this?
Man, that's two spells per cast is breaking my brain.
Fuck it, I don't want to do it.
We're going back to what it was.
If I can remember.
I think this was at the front.
Then we had a... this one there.
No, this was at the front, I think.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There, there, there, there.
Yeah, and then we had multiple of these.
This seems like the thing we had.
But I do want to... I do want to...
grab this one because it's actually kind of cool.
Do I want to grab it, though?
0.02, 0.25, 0.762 for 7.
Yeah, I want to grab it.
I want to grab it.
So let me put these here.
Exchange it.
And then take all of these.
Oh, this is going to be annoying.
There we go.
That works.
Let's move on.
That guy is very protected in there.
Current goal is to find...
a... digging wand.
That doesn't suck.
Oh, no.
Here we go again.
There's got to be a way to get through those fuckers.
Maybe, maybe Trivia Bolt just doesn't do any damage to him.
Maybe I need to try something else.
What about this?
Where are you?
Sir?
You like that?
Oh, my God.
He does not... He likes that.
He likes that.
What about we try this one?
We don't have limited of it?
Oh, yeah.
That works.
Why is this guy so resistant to that?
I don't understand.
Oh, my God.
I hate it.
I need to get out of here.
We're leaving.
I hate...
Something worse than spiders.
It's spiders that are fucking impossible to kill.
Yeah, just chill here.
It's fine.
Kill that guy.
Oh, my God.
It's chaos now.
Water, water, water, water, water.
Okay, calm down.
Calm down.
Oh, it's one of these guys again.
Wait, is it you?
See, now it's lagging again.
Because of the spider.
What?
Wait, what the fuck kind of creature is that?
Oh, no, he's stuck in terrain.
Watch.
Yep.
You see that?
Worked.
I think this is... I mean, I did damage the spider with that.
Let me try that again.
If I see the... Jesus!
Okay.
Yeah, I'm doing damage.
I'm doing damage.
Oh, my God, he has HP.
I hate this guy so much.
Fuck off, man.
This is the worst.
Is he summoning a spider?
What's happening?
What the fuck's going on?
I don't like this.
Oh, God, there's a thingy.
I think this thingy died.
Okay, there's a bunch of blood in here.
That's a healing source.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Oh, it's all this rotten meat.
Oh, that's bad.
Maybe I don't want to drink the blood of rotten meat.
That sounds bad to me.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah, I have healing for days here.
Lovely stuff.
Oh, don't get in the pool.
Just drink slowly.
I should probably not eat this.
Yeah, that's bad.
Don't eat.
That's damaging me, actually.
I see now.
There we go.
Nice and smooth.
Lovely.
Oh, yeah, this is good.
I kind of want to get rid of this rotten meat so I can drink this blood.
Oh, never mind.
There's a bunch of... Oh, this is a blood source.
Holy shit.
Love it.
Full HP, no problem.
Okay, this guy wants a piece.
Okay.
We're back on track.
Come on, wand.
I need digging.
Oh, my gosh.
This place is nuts.
I think this may be one of my least favorite levels.
It's just too chaotic for me.
Oh, no, that was a healer guy.
Well, whatever.
Oh, stop shooting.
Who is it?
It's you.
Why is my mana going?
Hold on.
There we go.
I was like, what the fuck?
Something is off here.
Now I get it.
For the longest time, like, wait a minute, something's off here.
Okay.
I'm just looking for that sweet outline of a wand in the distance, and I haven't seen it.
What's that?
How do you survive this place without a wand like this, huh?
Ah, wand.
Come on, that's got to be...
Shit.
I kind of want that, actually.
I want to experiment with that.
I want to experiment with...
Maybe have a freeze charge.
Maybe that will do something to the spider.
And charm untucked.
Makes it protect all charm creatures covered in toxic sludge.
Maybe.
Maybe that could be pretty dope.
We'll have to try.
But we would need a charm wand for that, something specific.
Tailor made for that sort of thing.
What is this?
Oh, nevermind, it's nothing.
Okay, someone shooting shit?
It is you.
Wand, wand, wand, wand.
Isn't it kind of crazy that I haven't... Ah, there we go.
Whoa, the party's all here.
Ah, hello.
What do we have here?
What do we have there?
Hold on.
Now the question is, what do we keep from here?
Ah, throw away.
Actually, water could be cool to have.
I regret it, take it back.
Let's throw away that.
Let's throw away this one.
That one, we have a bunch of these anyway.
Maybe throw away... ooh.
That one.
Throw away that one.
And maybe that one as well.
This one.
Throw away that one.
One of these.
That one.
And then these three go up here.
There we go.
Maybe I just keep this wand for storage.
Is that crazy?
This could be a storage.
This is quite big, isn't it?
Maybe it's okay to have a storage wand like this.
Like, something...
Right?
I need digging?
Teleport?
Damage.
What else do I need?
Nothing, because I can always hot-swap this shit.
I have Tinker.
Right?
So...
Whatever.
I wonder if this one will dig.
Let's leave this like that.
Now I just need to find a way to make this heal me.
Basically.
In fact, I may already have an idea.
Oh wait, it's shuffle.
Oh, that's crap.
Oh, that's fine.
We can always put these in something like this.
Oh, it's like a glowing lance.
I basically want to make it go up and fall down on me.
If I can make the projectile slow enough.
Ah, look at this!
This also...
Wait, does it work?
Hold on, let me get rid of this.
Oh wait, it disappears.
Huh.
Make it even slower.
What do I have?
I mean, I guess I could try this one again.
No, where is it?
Where's the thing I just had?
What?
Where's the phasing?
Am I blind?
Did I throw it over here somehow?
Not that one.
What the fuck?
Where did I...
Oh, whoa!
Aiming arc!
Wait, what?
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, it sort of works.
I just need to...
Where the fuck did my faith... Oh, there it is.
Okay, okay, I see, I see, I see.
We're gonna do this, that, that.
There.
Watch.
Excuse me?
Okay, man.
Yeah, how about no?
I will figure it out.
We will get to the bottom of this.
Oh, dude.
Maybe in water.
Everything slows down in water.
Uh, water, water, water, water, water.
Will that work?
Oh, you know what?
Let's not go into unexplored territory just yet.
Yeah, I'm just gonna move on right now.
It's fine.
We just need to find a big pool of water.
I think I can make it work.
Whoops!
I forgot, my wand's changed.
That is not, that is my digging.
Put this here.
There.
And this one goes there.
In fact, we could try this here.
Oh, that's messed up.
How about no?
I guess it does slow down the projectile quite a bit.
But it's cool.
The hell did I throw down here?
Oh, all kinds of shit.
Whatever.
Man, I can't believe it.
Are we actually leaving this place without a digging wand?
That's, there's no way.
Like, come on.
There's gotta be something.
I'm losing my mind here, Doc.
I can't even get through there?
No way.
Let's explore this place.
Oh, there used to be a portal here.
It's gone.
The spider.
The spider did it.
My God.
What an absolute mess this is.
These guys are just camping this portal.
Come on, next.
Drink the blood.
There's blood everywhere here.
Oh, that's toxic.
I haven't found a single heart in here, I don't think.
Those were very numerous in the jungle, but here, not so much.
This guy is stuck there.
I need to take a sip here.
Nice.
Who wants to taste my wand?
Come on now.
He likes, things have calmed down a little bit here in this place, and I appreciate that.
I think I just killed a friendo.
Oh, we're back.
Oh!
Neat.
Let me go grab some water, I guess.
We can test it here.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it doesn't work in water anyway.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay.
I think it does.
Let me add this as well.
No, no, wait.
This is shuffle.
It's shuffle.
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
Let's not forget that.
Wait, what?
Put that there.
Put this here.
There.
I don't understand.
Oh, almost.
Hmm.
I wonder if this shield is going to absorb it anyway when I try to heal with it.
Fuck.
Hey!
Did that work?
464.
Wait a minute.
Wait, why doesn't it...
Oh, it was the last!
I see.
I...
I took 30 damage?
Wait a minute.
464.
Huh?
I don't know.
Hold on.
What if I fall from here and go like that?
And then I catch up to it.
Huh.
Wait, is my shield disappearing?
Oh no, it's just in the water it disappears.
Okay.
Oh man, what the fuck?
Okay, I'm not sure.
Hmm.
That is a mystery.
We'll figure it out.
What did I do last time?
I think I had orbiting something and I made it work that way.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm not quite sure.
Anyway, let's get some water.
That's why I'm here.
And I can even do this.
Hey!
What a shortcut.
Hey, sir.
Your whole family is dead.
And you know what?
I enjoyed killing all of you.
Women, the children, everyone died.
Nope.
Not what I'm looking for.
Not my tempo.
What's that?
Piercing shot.
Oh, no, no, no.
No.
Thanks, though.
There's going to be a lot of blood here.
Dang.
Lovely, isn't it?
A good day for killing.
Drink all that.
All right, that's fine.
Come on, man.
Look at these fools in there.
It's time.
It's so cool.
Actually, there's kind of a feast in there.
Why can I not teleport it?
Oh, oh, that's why.
Drink it.
Drink that shit.
Ouch.
Man, I'm losing more HP than I'm getting because I'm taking this damage.
Sometimes this drinking the blood thing is not always...
All the rage, you know.
Oh, my God.
I'm taking more and more damage here.
I've been here before.
Nothing good.
I've been there before.
Where have I not been?
Oh, God, that's right.
Don't go in there.
All right.
I think I've explored this whole area.
Almost.
Ah, there's a one.
Oh, wait a minute.
I messed that one up.
Yeah.
Oh, and a chest.
Oh, nice.
Cool.
The one has more than 50 mana.
All mana over that.
Do...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is limited.
It's limited.
Yeah.
But you know what?
I think I won it just for that, for later, if I get infinite spells.
I do not remember if that actually affects it.
Or not.
Or if it's another one of those black hole situations.
Very well could be.
There's a chance.
What are you?
Okay.
I think it's time to leave, guys.
It's next.
We got to go to the next place.
Hopefully we'll find something that digs there.
It sounds crazy, but...
That's how it is.
Yeah, we got to go.
420 HP.
Wait a minute.
We have a god here.
Let's get ready.
Just wait for this to be done.
Whatever's going on there.
What?
No, not here.
Guys.
Come on, god.
Show yourself.
There he is.
Yeah, you're not an issue.
Fuck you and your angry anger anger.
More love.
I don't like any of these.
Oh.
Nope.
I don't like any of those.
Floating corpses.
Extra life.
Oh, that's...
That's not bad.
Item radar.
Hmm.
Nope.
Attract gold.
Toxic immunity.
No.
Yes.
Fuck toxic.
We're done with that.
Holy shit.
Okay.
I think I may want to buy none of these because guess what?
I used all my money.
I'm going to go over here now.
Boink.
Okay, now.
My only goal.
Oh, by the way.
Look at this.
This is depicting the final boss, isn't it?
Look at that.
That looks exactly like the boss.
With all the legs and all that.
Creepy legs.
Anyway, what I was saying...
was that...
The only objective right now is to find a wand that can dig.
Because I don't care about winning.
I want to get up top again and explore.
Is there a way to kill those guys, man?
Ah, they're so annoying.
Look at all this gold dropping though.
I don't enjoy lava.
Those things are dangerous.
They shoot some crazy stuff.
Wow, that guy needed some hits.
Wait.
What's happening here?
Maybe nothing.
Come on.
What?
Oh, I hit one of those crystals.
For a brief second there, I don't know how, but my brain instantly went...
Wait, am I suddenly cursed and this thing is following me around?
Ah, what the hell?
Oh, it's this thing.
Get him out of here.
Wait, is the blood also forming a rock on top of the lava?
I think it is.
Now I can drink this blood.
What, what, what, what, what?
Wait, what's happening there?
Why, why, why?
Huh?
I'm afraid of drinking blood.
And now this guy is on me.
Why is that happening?
I don't understand.
Drink here.
Okay, here I can drink.
Huh?
Oh yeah, I'm getting a lot of blood here.
This is great.
Oh, no, no, no.
Maybe if you drink too much.
What the fuck?
Wait, what does this actually say?
Hold on.
You lose 25% of maximum health, but can replenish health by drinking blood.
Blood doesn't affect satiation level.
Oh!
And you no longer suffer from... Wait, it doesn't affect satiation level.
How was I satiated... I guess I must have drunk something else, like water.
Like what the f...
Why is...
I'm afraid of it suddenly making lightning.
That's the thing I'm afraid of.
Don't lightning me.
Maybe it's telling me don't be too greedy with the blood, you know?
Like, okay, we get it, you can heal forever, but don't overdo it.
And here's fine.
What?
Alright, whatever.
Can I eat this green crystal?
Okay, maybe not.
Come on, show me the wands.
I require to... look at your wands, sir.
Very peaceful here, though, and I appreciate that.
After what we went through just before.
That was a shit show in the vault.
Glad that that's over.
598 HP, that's a decent amount.
Uh, hello, sir.
You are dead now.
Uh-oh.
All kinds of crap.
Guys, what happens if I never find something that fucking digs?
I'm gonna be stuck here forever.
That would be so sad, imagine.
Nah, that's gotta be a... I mean, I could technically wait by chance for a spider to dig all the way up.
Or, dude, maybe I can even...
Yo, I just had an idea.
Pheromone.
We put pheromone on a spider, worst case.
Make it follow us and make it dig.
We force it to dig, we only need to have it dig once.
Only up to snowy depths, and then we're good, actually.
Think about it.
Uh, why is this thing...
This thing is weird because it follows me, but then when it comes close it's like...
Oh, never mind, it is actually after me.
Look, this is another depiction of the final boss.
Wait a minute, this looks...
This looks odd!
Hold on, something's going on here.
What's happening here?
This looks like the, uh, the oil situation.
Something flows down here?
Into this?
I need to examine that in more detail when this fucking guy leaves me alone.
Whoa!
Get rid of me.
Get rid of me, I mean, get rid of you.
I get rid of you.
I can't speak.
Oh my god!
I'm taking some damage here.
Want!
Okay, guys, I need you to pray.
Pray with me.
Uhhh, hello, what the fuck is that?
I don't like that.
No, sir.
Aww.
Fuck.
That's not what I was looking for.
I am scared to death.
Don't even care about the gold anymore.
All I need is a lowly plasma cutter.
Can I has plasma cutter, sir, please?
Or a black hole.
I think a little black hole will do, sir.
Singula black hole.
That's a scorpion.
Oh!
Almost walked into that projectile there.
That was scary.
Is there anything up here?
No, that's all dense rock.
I want to go that way.
That was a trap.
It does feel good to just slay everybody in here.
Last time I was here, I had to go through invisible with 1 HP, remember?
That was a bit of a disaster.
That was fun, though.
That was a good run.
Now, what's happening there?
That's lava.
That's not good.
Bro, is this guy just following me everywhere?
Okay, so maybe he's not on my heels anymore.
I can go back and experiment with that place I found.
Wait a minute, this also looks interesting now.
Unstable polymorphine.
Uh-oh.
No, sir.
Oh, man, they're everywhere.
I obviously have to put something in here and it will flow down this channel into here.
This is all gone.
Oh, you know what?
We need to put lava in there.
Lava will affect gunpowder.
I'm pretty sure.
Something that blows things up, right?
And then something will happen.
Actually, there's lava right there, but I can't really pick it up, can I?
There's a wand!
This is my chance.
This is my ticket out of here.
Let's wait for this guy to come here, and then we go like that.
What have we got?
Holy lands.
Wait.
Penetrating lands?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, wait.
Lightning thrower?
No, thanks.
We're not doing that.
Oh, no, it doesn't penetrate anything.
But I am gonna steal one of them.
Oh, my God.
Get away from me, will ya?
Oh!
What's happening?
Huh?
Oh, neutralized spells!
Oh!
I see.
It was this guy's doing.
Okay, so, yeah, we have one of those now, and now we put it back.
Now we go.
Take through all of this.
Oh, that hurt.
That hurt a lot.
What's that?
Concentrated mana?
No, thanks.
I really hate these things.
They give me paranoia.
I can't relax.
Fuck off, man.
Leave me alone.
Oh, I've been here.
Chili egg?
Wait, maybe I can pheromone this dude.
Probably not, right?
He's like a ghost.
It's gonna face right...
Okay, he seems to be leaving me alone.
Let's just keep it that way.
He's not following me anymore.
What's happening?
I heard a wand.
Where?
Where was this guy?
I heard him.
In here?
Sir?
Oops.
Where?
There's a trap somewhere.
Oh, there you are.
Oh, wait a minute!
Yo, look at him!
He's sort of absorbing the spells.
Did he die?
I have no clue what just happened.
Oh, wait.
There we go.
Okay, you know what?
All things considered, I don't know why I'm stressing so much.
We're doing great, man.
Like, I can heal with the blood.
I have great wands.
I just need to be patient.
We'll find something.
Now I can drink this blood as well.
I need to calm down here.
It's happening.
We're doing this.
Oh, what?
Am I eating something specific that I'm not supposed to?
What's happening?
Maybe don't eat brickwork.
Maybe the gods are super angry about eating.
They're like, okay, destroying the brickwork makes us angry.
But eating it, boy oh boy, we're gonna come after you.
I don't know.
It's a joke.
It's probably not what's happening, but it's funny.
Oh, my God.
Those things need some shots, huh?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You fuck off.
You fuck off right now.
What?
That is such a funny spell.
Who makes that?
Oh, is it you?
You're the one making that.
It's like a weird poop.
He's pooping in a weird manner.
This still looks like a black hole to me.
It's a crystal.
Oh, no, not one of these.
Yeah.
Let me
go over here.
What will I find?
What's this?
Anyway, there's stuff up there.
Oh, yeah, there's stuff up here.
That was a lot of stuff.
Oh, another big ghost.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look at this number four again.
Same as four on these little alters where you usually find wands.
I don't know if that means anything.
Maybe it's not even the number.
It's just a symbol in this world, you know?
Digging.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
Is it winking at me?
Look.
Look at its eyes.
It's double winking.
It's like, you can't get past here, huh?
Wink, wink.
Fuck you, man.
I can teleport.
I don't give a shit about you.
I mean, I give a little shit.
I would say a tiny poop in your name.
But that's it.
All that gold, man.
I am rich.
I am... wait, oh.
Oh!
What's happening?
I'm stunned.
Oh, I was electrocuted.
Let's calm down, calm down, calm down, calm down.
Kill those guys, kill this guy.
Wait for this guy to come up here and then we teleport down.
Except he's sort of...
doesn't care about me right now for some reason.
Drink, drink.
Why is this happening?
Wait, how did this guy die?
Oh, he stood on the... toxic shit.
Good warning to me as well.
Don't stand on it.
Man, what would I do without the long-distance teleport right now, huh?
Okay, I'm gonna drink this blood.
I don't care if there's a cloud on me.
What if I keep drinking?
Come on, strike me down, strike me down.
I don't care.
Fuck your crystals too.
Yeah, I drink your brickwork.
Weird gravity on that.
Yeah, come on, rain on me.
I don't care.
That's fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wonder why that's happening.
I'm so confused.
I cannot think of anything that would cause that.
Oh, what's going on here?
I think it's time to find another syphilis.
There's a mage.
I'm scared of those.
He dead.
Next.
Why did I stop right there?
That's annoying.
Keep going, guys.
Come on.
Come to me.
Come this way.
Whoa!
Alright, this thing is scaring me.
I remember this.
It's reflecting my shit, I think.
Yeah, it totally is.
Okay, that works.
Shoot a couple shots off and move in a dodging manner while you shoot.
So that's such that you are like, dodge your own projectiles.
That's the method there.
I have 11 kick-old!
Damn!
I want to spend it on so many drilling bits.
Very hard drilling bits, though.
Oh, I can't kill that guy.
Fuck.
Eh.
Whoa, everything's collapsed here.
Oh, wait, I've been here.
I did that.
Going here.
Whoa!
Holy shit.
Kill that dude.
Blue sand?
Eat it.
Okay, doesn't do anything.
Fuck your crystals.
Oh, man.
I'm actually getting low here.
I need to find a good pool of blood and I just need to sit down and consume.
A good old feasting session.
Hello?
Wait a minute.
Can I actually... Hold on.
Let's get rid of this.
Can I drink it straight?
Oh!
Yo, that's a huge discovery!
Dude!
That's huge!
Oh, man.
Oh, wait, I can't think through that.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Oh, man.
So, okay, from now on, I'm just going to pick it up with my bottle and drink it straight out of the bottle.
That is big news.
I'm so happy I discovered that.
Oh, that makes me so happy, actually.
Look at this.
We collect all the blood.
We don't care about the cloud, whatever.
Oh, yeah, it's getting filled.
Fill it up.
Oh, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
And then we just...
Oh, that's so beautiful.
It's basically a healing potion now.
That's what it is.
I accidentally filled up my water bottle with a bit of blood there, but that's fine.
Oh, don't get into the lava.
Be careful now.
That blood looks chunky.
Oh, this is so much better.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm so happy about this.
Mmm!
It's also faster.
Beautiful.
Look at that.
Oh, man.
Here we are.
Drink all that.
Almost 500 HP again.
Lovely!
That's amazing.
Oh, that's teleportation.
Let's not touch that.
That scares me.
Yes, dude!
We're back on track, baby!
That is just lovely.
Okay, you go away.
Fuck.
Get out of here.
That's for you.
Whoa!
That was a bit scary.
Don't stand in that, you dummy.
Bad idea.
Severe lack of ones in this place.
I'm just going to say that outright.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
That projectile is the worst.
Collect the blood.
Sweet, sweet blood.
And the thing is... Wait, what?
Oh, I'm confused because I ingested ambiguous meat.
Okay.
Whoops, there must have been something else in that potion.
Yeah, a couple of bugs get in there.
It doesn't matter.
We eat that.
It's funny.
It's only when I eat off the ground that it starts raining on me.
Like, what the hell does that mean?
It's only started happening in the last couple of levels.
No, don't go up there.
What's happening here?
Oh no, wrong spell.
I was going to go up here.
I love digging.
What's that?
My God.
The hammers is happy.
You love to see that.
I'll leave them alive.
Happy hammers means happy life.
Look at me cleansing this place like a pro.
Okay, so that's the portal to the end.
I don't want to take it, man.
I don't.
Give me the...
Ah, hey, that's something.
Come here.
Come here, you fucker.
Actually, no, no, no.
I'm going to drink blood.
Oh, I love all this blood.
I love all this blood.
Fuck off, man.
Okay, he seems like he doesn't care about me while I'm standing here.
That's weird.
And then he cares about me suddenly.
And then...
What's up with you, man?
Stop it.
Leave me.
God, that massive creature scared the crap out of me.
I do not want to fight him.
What is in these, by the way?
Oh, blue sand.
Fuck you.
What's in here?
Ah, that's cursed.
I don't want to fuck with that.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We don't do that here.
Nope.
No more blood?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Ah.
What do we have here?
Hey, look at that!
Wait, what did I get?
Wait, equipped wand?
Wait, what just happened?
It said...
It said equipped wand in the messages.
I'm so confused right now.
Wait, is there a wand down here?
Did a wand fall out?
Oops.
Oh, this is teleportation.
Or like polymorphism.
Let's just wait it out.
There we go.
Yeah, we don't want polymorphine.
That's bad.
That's real.
Ooh.
Wait, is that mine?
Did I leave it here?
In all the mountains...
Oh yeah, this is the one I left here.
Okay, we're back.
But we haven't gone this way.
This is new.
There's still a chance.
Honestly, maybe if I go up again, there is a path upwards to snowy depths just because we've spent so much time here and maybe there's been a worm in the meanwhile.
You know, it's possible.
There's a chance.
Don't shoot that shit at me.
Speaking of...
Should I even go up here?
This is definitely the work of a spider, a massive spider.
I'm scared of...
I'm not going to teleport.
I'm scared of that.
If I instantly teleport into something undesirable, that would take away from my happen as well.
Which is currently quite full.
But not...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck you!
Next!
Wait.
I'm hearing...
sound.
I'm hearing sound here.
Oh, I wish I could dig.
There's something here.
Can I really not dig somehow?
Hold on.
I haven't tried this plasma beam bounce, actually.
Let's see.
A projectile launches a plasma beam upon bouncing.
Okay.
Very scary, though, because it shoots it off in random directions.
It works, technically.
It works.
But I don't trust that at all.
I'm kind of relieved.
Honestly, this means there is a chance for us getting out, like, completely.
You know?
Which is nice.
Yeah, let's not have that in here right now.
Or should I?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, wait.
I'm an idiot.
The sound comes from up here.
Oh, wait.
Is it the ominous liquid making that sound?
Oh!
Is that really true?
Hold on.
Can I...
do something to it?
Let's try and get rid of it.
I want to confirm this.
Get out of here.
Does it even do anything?
Transmute drops of water from nothing.
This is very slight.
I'm not quite sure I understand this spell.
Yeah, that spell makes no sense to me.
Like, what?
Also, I don't want to be in here.
I don't want the spiders.
I need to make my way out.
Now I'm back here.
Okay, you know what?
Actually, there's a good chance, if anything.
So, I know how to get to the level above here, actually.
Okay, this is what we're gonna do.
Go down here.
Wait, how do I just...
Was it up here?
Uh, here.
Oops.
I'm gonna go up to the level above.
Oh yeah, here we go, here we go.
I know how to get up there.
Oh wait, that's actually more stuff I haven't explored.
BLOOD!
Lots of it!
Hallelujah, baby!
That's big!
Oh, this is full health.
This is easy, full health!
Wait, what?
What just happened?
What was that sound?
I think there was something in my bottle that shouldn't have been there.
Again.
But oh, don't touch the molten metal.
Why am I getting ominous music?
Full health, baby.
We are so back.
Wild.
What's in here?
Oil.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Over here, over here.
Oh wait, I can't.
Ah, nice.
Beautiful.
Okay, now watch this.
That looks like a ball sack.
Okay, so we made it here.
Now we just need to find a way from the jungle and up.
If we can do that, we're home free.
We don't need a digging.
Maybe there's a spider or a worm somewhere here that did something while we were gone.
That's what I'm hoping for.
Actually, you know what?
But we could also explore the rest of this place anyway.
Maybe there's a wand here that will do digging.
No?
I don't recall whether or not we explored this whole place.
Let's just go up and check first.
Maybe we get lucky.
Here, here, here.
Can I not?
Wait.
Shit.
Ah, wait, maybe here.
Yeah!
Beautiful.
And now, can I somewhere do a nice teleport?
Is there anything in here that will dig?
Not sure.
It doesn't look like it, guys.
Whoops, I didn't mean to do that.
That's fine.
You know, this thing has kind of collapsed now.
Maybe that's good.
Hold on.
Can I barely inch my way up there somehow?
What was that sound?
You heard that?
Sounded like a...
What?
What was that?
I have no idea what's happening.
Let's see if we can't find a place where there's a hole through here.
Oh, wait, a worm's been here.
Oh!
Oh, wait, I'm an idiot.
I killed that fucking worm.
Whoops.
Oh, I get it!
No way, I don't get it, no mind.
I thought I knew why we got that effect when we drank, but I don't understand why.
Nothing here.
What's this wand again?
Nothing on it.
Man!
There's gotta be some way.
What do I... Actually, there is a way.
You know what?
I'm gonna try with the plasma beam.
Because here's the deal.
We need to make a... Okay, I have a great idea.
I have the perfect idea.
A safe idea, too.
Watch.
I'm gonna show you.
It's gonna be glorious.
And super safe, too.
I'm not gonna take... I'm not gonna take any damage from this.
This is genius.
Wait till you see it.
Wait, how do I get out again?
Where's the... There we go.
Watch.
This is the plan.
We are gonna do... this one.
Uh, here?
Hold on.
There.
Okay.
Long distance.
And then we're gonna do... Well, I guess that's fine.
Modifier.
Just organize these a bit.
There we go.
That one there.
This one can go here.
Why not?
Okay.
So, I'm gonna throw this inside of the... Wait.
When it bounces.
Does this bounce?
Oh, wait.
Oh, that's actually funny, though.
Okay, that doesn't bounce.
So, how about we do...
Yeah.
Oh!
Okay, that's scary.
That is scary.
It sort of... It creates it multiple places.
I don't like... I think it's because of the triplicate.
We don't need triplicate.
We need something else that bounces.
Does this count as a bounce?
It doesn't.
What about this one?
No?
Hmm.
Let's think.
What else do... Maybe the heal?
It's gonna sound dumb.
No.
Hmm.
This is a dumb situation to be in.
I feel like it's really dumb.
You know?
Like, gah!
I wanna get out of here!
Let me out of here!
Uh... Hold on.
What else do I have?
Lightning... Maybe this one.
Oh, fly slower?
That's not even digging anything!
This is the most tough digging ever.
I mean, it works.
I could do it.
It's just gonna take a long time.
It's not fun.
I don't know, man.
I'm not feeling it.
I'm not.
Let's put this one back somewhere... there.
This one is what we had there.
And then we had a chainsaw.
There.
That's our digging.
Let's just make a little path here.
How about... energy home-bringer?
Dammit.
If only I had the disc projectile orbit thing, that would dig.
Okay, instead of sitting here crying about it, let's go find a wand.
Sitting here is not gonna do anything.
We need to find something.
Hey, buddy!
See, this guy can't kill!
And I think it's because there's no friendly fire on my wand.
We can also... Oh, we have full water.
I mean, blood.
I was about to say a worm has been here, but that's me.
I've been here.
I made that hole.
Let me try and see if there isn't a path made somewhere up northwest somewhere.
We just need to find one place, right?
Hey, hold on.
There's a spider there.
But it's not one of those that dig, I don't think.
Okay, time for the second plan.
It's pheromone time.
We're gonna try... and pheromone a spider.
You can try this at home.
You can be just like me.
Oh, god.
I'm gonna pheromone this guy and bring him with me.
Or maybe aggro him and bring him with me.
That's the plan.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, come here.
Oh, they're already digging.
Look, look, look, look.
You like that?
Yeah, you like pheromone?
Pheromone!
Pheromone for you!
Yeah, it's not working.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, you're angry now.
I'm hitting you.
You don't like that at all, do you?
Oh, yeah, you're scared for some reason.
Oh, you know what?
I haven't explored the spider cave here.
Maybe there's a wand in here that can dig.
That's actually a possibility.
It's scary, but it's there, you know.
It's a thing.
Uh-oh.
Wait, he has ambrosia on.
Not anymore.
I could get high and just forget about my problems.
Hey, that's dope.
Very cool.
I'm so scared being in here.
What the hell is this?
Dude.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to take it.
I mean, I did, but, you know.
Okay, he leaves me alone.
Oh, that... Oh, no.
My wand is gone.
No, wait, it's there.
I see it, I see it, I see it.
Hey, guys, come here.
Okay, leave, leave, please, so I can...
snatch my wand.
At least time stand stills when you activate that.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
Got it.
Dude, I just realized I tensed my whole body just now.
Oh, I need to calm down.
I need to purposefully calm down here.
Wand.
Oh, no.
You know what?
Maybe the bomb cards will dig.
Think about it.
Bomb card?
Oh.
Bomb cards is like related to mining and shit, right?
Like mine cards.
What are the chances this will dig?
Uh, Jared, replace that shit.
We're gonna try it at some point.
We have six of them.
If it works, we can come back here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hello, hello, hello.
Oh, almost.
Whoever dug here should have kept digging.
Damn.
That's ominous.
That's no bueno.
Wait, I can't... Oh, this is very tough stuff to get through.
What's happening in there?
Someone is shooting a wand?
I don't like the look of that.
But I'm gonna go in there anyway.
Is that you?
Oh, black hole!
My dude has a black hole!
Don't use them all.
Don't fucking use them all, you piece of shit.
And he's ambrosia'd up.
There we go, buddy.
There we go.
Salvation!
We made it!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
We're not out of the woods yet.
We need to safely transfer.
No, don't put it there.
Put it there, throw that away.
Put it there, throw this away.
Put it...
This one can go away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Replace it back.
Fuck yeah, man!
And we even have spell refresh!
Ah!
Let's get the fuck out of here.
I had enough of this place.
My god, there it is!
Alright!
Let's go!
We only need those three.
I'm gonna dig straight up, I think.
Oh, dude!
Let's try this.
Look, it talked to here, but with this on?
Yes!
We fucking made it, that's awesome!
Oh, wait!
We need to get one level higher, but that's fine.
We have plenty of black holes.
Yeah, that's fine.
In fact, let's grab the refresher here.
Should I?
Yeah, yeah, why not.
Yeah, yep, we grabbed the refresher here.
No, we're not... oh no, we're saving it.
We're saving that for later.
I believe I can do this with one single black hole.
Because... yeah, I believe.
Watch me.
It's gonna happen.
It's gonna be glorious!
Let's find the highest point.
Maybe over there.
Also, we have a refresh here if we need it, so...
I'm gonna be jumping as well to give it extra momentum.
Okay, here we go.
Look at that!
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't...
Amazing.
Well, I'm back, boys!
Let's go again.
Don't you fucking shoot that at me.
No!
Okay, that's fine.
That's fine.
We made it.
And you know what?
This is the place we never fully explored.
We can do that now.
Also, did I change something here?
Oh yeah, right.
I forgot this.
Like, that felt off somehow.
Look at that next... next to a wand.
If there's a black hole in here, I'm gonna scream.
Okay, I'm not gonna scream, don't worry.
Okay.
Now I can explore this place completely.
What a run so far, huh?
Very exciting stuff.
I love it.
Did I do this?
I was digging here, I think.
Oh, now I don't have that anymore.
We need to change this up again.
What's in here?
I always feel like they're hiding stuff in these piles.
Whoa!
Whoa, don't go through that.
Look at all this snow, there's gotta be something hidden.
Maybe not.
Another wand?
Okay, cool.
No thanks.
Ah, we... oh, we can get in here now.
Yeah!
I don't want any of this though.
Or do I?
Wait a minute, is this a trap?
Hold on.
Am I being punked?
Is this connected to something?
Somewhere?
I think I'm fine.
I don't see a trap.
Take one of these.
Oh, I had an extra black hole anyway!
I didn't notice that.
Oh, nice.
Pretty cool.
Let's replace that.
I don't want this.
This is way too chaotic for me.
Let's get another one of these and then throw this one away.
No, just put some here.
Actually, do it out here instead.
There we go.
And then this wand can go away.
Because, I just want to see how this is gonna feel.
Dope.
Oh, that's cool.
Lot of recoil though.
How much damage is that?
Thirteen damage.
And this one does five damage, but there's three of them, so fifteen.
It's almost as much, right?
But thirty mana drain, twenty-five.
Yeah.
But I guess we don't need reduced spread on it then.
Right?
Ah, we actually do.
The wand itself has a bit of spread and I guess some things are adding spread?
This one adds a bit of spread to it.
Ah, fuck it.
I mean, we're gonna hold on to this though.
Let's throw that one out.
We don't need three of them.
I like that.
It's solid, it works, you know what you're getting for your money.
And I can drink my blood.
Sweet.
Look at the speed at which we can explore this place now.
Insano style is what this is.
Blood- Hey, nice!
Wait, why can't I...
There we go.
And then put this here.
Wait, did I just throw away?
What did I just throw away?
It's probably fine.
Whoa, that guy came out of nowhere.
Right, this place was dark!
That's why I can't recognize where I've been.
Oh, dear lordy.
I have no idea where I'm going.
Huh.
I guess this must have been one of mine.
Yo.
Nah.
That's the entrance?
I'm like a worm, man.
Sweet.
You know what I could do?
I could go all the way down to the last level now, get a perk, and then come up.
There's still a perk to be had, I think, and we have black holes, so...
Right?
I know I just came up here, but...
Like, having a whole new perk would be crazy.
Potentially more than one, by the way.
Because of the perk lottery.
Boink.
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay.
Oh, wait a minute!
I have toxic immunity!
I just...
Holy shit!
Nice!
I forgot about that.
I was avoiding these all the time.
I completely forgot about that.
Bro!
Yo!
Look at that!
I don't even know what I want anymore.
I want this, like...
Fuck off.
Maybe I don't want freeze charge.
Maybe I do want freeze charge.
I want to keep this here.
The rest I don't care about, I don't think.
What do I not want?
Maybe this one.
Put this up here.
I mean, I have so many healing.
Do I really need this many?
Let's get rid of this one, too.
Maybe it's blasphemous.
I don't know.
But I have enough.
Plus I can heal with blood, right?
Hold on.
Give me blood.
Nice.
Very ominous ambiance right now, too.
Oh, that's right!
There's this place!
Hey, what's up?
What's up?
Heel's blooming here?
I don't care.
We're going.
We are going.
I'm not scared of anything.
I have a sick shit ton of HP here, bro.
Nothing can compete with me!
Top of the game, remember the name.
You guys are lame.
Whoops.
Let's not kill myself.
That would be preferable here.
Go slow.
Whoa!
Someone's shooting some shit.
Show yourself!
Sir?
At least I'm slowly revealing this place by walking through it.
What is this stuff?
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Fuck you!
Where's that guy that shot at me?
Was that... I think I got him.
Hello, Mr. Brain Man!
He looks crazy.
Like he has a blood tumor for a head.
Okay.
Hey!
I see you.
Wait, I can dig through this.
No, wait.
Wait, actually?
Holy shit!
Wait, isn't this...
Oh, it's just... Oh, wow.
Wait.
Why am I...
This is... It's not dense break work, though.
I can't... This is not...
Yeah.
Okay, there's this.
Orb room.
Sure.
Thank you.
Familiar orb of true knowledge.
Thank you very much.
I feel completely filled with all the correct knowledge and not at all the fake knowledge.
No fake news in me.
Still don't know what that means.
Yeah.
Someone's angry down below.
Or above.
Maybe that means the same thing.
In this world.
Okay, that's the bottom.
I still have my worm blood, by the way, when we get to the dark cave.
Oh, that's interesting.
If you teleport, you're not actually going to reveal through the distance you teleport.
Only at your location where you appear.
Oh, that guy's up there somewhere.
Okay, we're in this place again, so there's some kind of pyramid here.
What's happening?
Holy shit.
Things just started exploding.
Someone else is here.
Are you dead?
I see gold falling.
Oh, yeah, he died.
He did.
Oh, wow.
I mean, if I was here earlier, I would be salivating over this, but not anymore.
Don't care.
Oh, wait.
Oh, but wait, I can do this.
I can do this.
I don't know why that guy just scared me so much.
I need to go to heart attack.
Here's that book again.
Book of celestial bodies.
As with everything else.
Every celestial body also has its counterpart.
For every golden star is a dark enigma.
And for every silvery moon, there is a hollow shadow.
I can't stop thinking about...
...anti-particles.
Wait, oh, this is the music thingy.
Do I want that?
Maybe a...
You know what?
Yeah, let's take it with us.
Put on the tunes.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so there's a counterpart.
This... Okay, you know what, actually?
Maybe this is somehow telling me that I need to connect...
...the two parts.
Like the moon and the hollow shadow.
Or in this case, the music...
...with the music in the tree, maybe.
Maybe I need to bring this to the...
Or put this in the music wand that is inside the tree.
This artifact is covered in note-shaped engravings and is pulsing at a steady pace.
Is that the sound of distant music?
So distant music...
It could mean that simply because when I equip this I can hear music.
Or it could mean leading me to, hey, there's somewhere else in this world where there's music distant away.
You know, like it's far away in the distant land.
Meaning the tree, maybe.
I'm very intrigued about this.
What does that mean?
Hmm.
Very curious.
Let me see again.
It's with everything else.
Every celestial body.
Do we know of any celestial bodies in this game?
Other than the earth that we are upon?
Where every golden star is a dark enigma.
Like a black hole?
Black hole.
And for every silvery moon there's a hollow shadow.
Moon.
Dark side of the moon?
Or a shadow version of the moon?
Interesting.
I'm gonna move on for now.
I think I may go down all the way, grab the perk and then head back up.
That seems prudent.
Also, I'm using the word prudent in a way that I think is correct.
But I actually don't know what that word means.
I've only heard it in contexts and I think I used it correctly there.
Even though I don't know what it means.
You can... Oh, wait.
That's the one right here.
Oh, I missed that.
Wild.
Why did that just take so much damage?
Oh, I was drowning, I think.
It was the drowning damage.
Lack of O2, baby.
That'll get you.
Alright, let's see how fast I can speedrun through this.
Ah, shit, I can't do that from here.
Doink, doink, doink, doink, doink, doink, doink.
You know what, I should fill up my... my blood bottle.
And then I should also fill up my water bottle.
Look at all this blood.
Dude, vampirism is sick.
One of my favorite perks now.
Absolutely incredible S-tier perk for me.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
This one too.
Grab a bit there.
Oh, man, look at all this blood.
Wait, what was this, wand?
Oh, thanks.
On we go, on we go.
Doink.
That mine can't die for some reason.
Okay, there we go.
I tried for so long, but he wouldn't want to die.
I could get high.
But I'm not gonna.
We're gonna stay sober.
Wow, that was fast.
And we go down, like that, doink, doink, doink.
There may still be enemies here, I gotta be careful.
I surely did not clear this entire place.
I guess I may as well do that, since I'm here.
And look at that, a wand too, and a mage.
Oh, god.
Uh, no.
Yeah, just go, go, go, go, go, go.
Get in, get in.
That's fine, that's fine, that's fine.
Fell out my water bottle.
Okay.
What's that?
No, if only I had the opposite.
Wait, chainspell?
Dude, will you go away?
Let's leave one of these here and, uh...
Let me try that.
What's this?
Causes a projectile to cast a copy of itself when expiring up to...
Yo!
Black hole?
Is that gonna consume extra black holes?
Is that like five, one to five?
That's crazy if that's the case.
Can I make five black holes out of one black hole?
Imagine.
Also, I don't remember if I've tried that one before.
I feel like I may have seen it before, but I'm not entirely sure.
Something similar to it, at least.
Also, stop that.
Oh, god.
There's gotta be a way to take care of these guys.
Just don't know what it is.
What's that?
Concentrated mana.
You know what, I should drink my blood.
Absolutely no reason not to.
Mm-hmm.
Make it safe to traverse.
Hello.
What's up, people?
I have returned.
Just here for a quick stint.
To find some perks and then I'm gone again.
Oh, here it is.
Support that has been found.
Let's do it.
The laboratory.
Let's see what we got.
Wait a minute.
What is that?
Null shot.
Increases a projectile's duration dramatically.
But removes all damage and explosion from it.
Black hole?
That's a black hole modifier.
Random damage?
Randomly increases or lowers the damage done by projectiles.
Uh...
Oh, but it...
So, but it has a base damage of plus ten more.
So, on average, the casino doesn't win, you win.
If that makes sense.
That's intriguing.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, I almost forgot about that guy.
Wait, the gods are enraged?
Uh-oh.
What does that mean?
Oh, no.
Oil blood?
Let me...
Ooh.
Ooh!
Oh, that...
That's good!
Levitation trail?
Revenge rats?
Amunculus?
I think I want to take this, man.
Is that crazy?
I could also re-roll.
Ooh.
Hold on.
That...
Amunculus sucks.
This also sucks.
Dude, being immune to fire would be quite the thing.
But wait, wait, wait, wait.
I bleed flammable oil.
I need to bleed blood because I'm vampire.
You know what?
No, we're not doing that.
We're re-rolling.
Re-rolling.
Trick greed.
Oh, no.
All these suck.
I have done a dumb thing.
Your spells knock enemies around with more force.
No!
Shit!
These all suck.
Okay, hold on.
We need 12,000 gold...
Bro.
Oh, no.
I'm coming back to re-roll that later.
That's going to be a long-term project there.
I can tell you that much.
So here's what I'm going to do, though.
For now...
I am gonna...
do this.
Actually, I'm going to test with this first.
Just a singular.
There.
And then...
Ah, wait, now I don't have money for this one.
Okay, whatever.
That's fine.
It's not, though.
You know what I mean?
It's not fine.
I'm suffering.
It's really tough.
And then we need this one.
Let's try it!
Make it right here.
Boom!
The gods are very angry with you.
And I got a fucking achievement.
Why?
I thought I turned that off.
I hate that.
Okay.
I made them very angry now.
I don't know what that means, but now I'm really scared.
Can we have peace now?
Please?
Peace?
Peace, please?
Where's that lava coming from?
Oh, I don't want that dripping down into my...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That stops right here.
I don't do that.
So basically the plan now...
Wait, what the hell?
Wait, where am I?
Oh, I'm at the very edge of this place.
The plan is to go back up.
I want to go to the ancient laboratory now.
Because I have a bone to pick with a certain someone there.
And then I also want to go to the dark cave.
I want to go there first.
Yeah, let's go there first.
And then we go to the ancient laboratory afterwards.
And there's a wand there.
Sweet.
Sweet stuff.
But it sucks, so I don't care.
Wait a minute.
Whoa!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's happening?
What?
Hold on.
Put this here.
What the fuck is that?
What?
I can dig through dense rock?
I can't through extremely, right?
No, okay.
What the?
Okay, that's a surprise.
Oh, oh, that's extremely dense.
It's an egg.
Oh, no, wait.
I have no more black holes.
Oh, whoa, it has a force field.
Look at that.
What?
Huh?
Huh.
By the way, this egg, I'm pretty sure was in the intro cinematic.
There was a bunch of stuff with that, remember?
One of them was an egg and then it cracked open and then something happened.
This guy is scared of it.
He doesn't want to come close at all, look.
Should I bring an egg here?
What the fuck is happening here, bro?
Oh, man, I wish I could...
Okay, I'm going to...
Oh, man.
What can I do here?
I think I'm going to need to get a black hole and shoot it through here just to see what's inside.
Oh, but actually, no.
The black hole will consume.
So what I really need is a plasma cutter.
Oh, but will the force field work against me still?
That's like the problem, right?
Hold on, let me grab this one real quick.
There it is!
That's my black hole, thank you.
Sawblade orbit!
Lovely!
I take that.
Very much, thank you very much.
Oh, you bastard.
Get away from me.
Okay, I'm going to put this here for now.
Let's just throw these on the floor here in case we want them later.
Look, he's scared of this place.
He doesn't want...
The fuck I stole my one!
Oh, no!
Oh!
I'm getting low here, I...
I don't know if I should do this with low health.
I'm too scared.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I've been playing for a lot right now, so I'm going to do this.
I'm going to exit.
I'm going to switch over to my map.
And I'm going to quickly remind myself what just happened.
So hold on.
Let's grab the old pen.
Okay, so I am right now in...
I am in...
What was it called?
Basically the place below here.
That's where I am.
Something like that.
Let me separate it a bit more to make it nice.
And then, in the bottom right, we have a bit of a triangle.
It's sort of embedded in...
I want to say, like, right...
Hold on, let me zoom in.
Let's do that.
Ah, more like...
I just want to make it nice, that's all.
Embedded in the rock there.
Something like that.
And this place is called...
Ah, what was it?
The laboratory was below.
In fact, I need to put that on the map as well.
This place is called the dream or something.
What was it?
Hold on.
The act, the art.
Something like that.
Oh,
nice.
Make it a bit bigger.
There we go.
In fact, another thing I want to do now is...
So the vault and underground jungle, they actually connect via the looky layer.
I want to put that on right now.
That's this one.
Rectangle.
It's like...
I want to say something like...
That, in a way.
That's fine.
And then there's, like, an axis, I guess, between them.
We're going to make a little hole.
Like that.
And I guess there's, like, something...
So I have to confirm this.
I guess I'm going to look at the vault after this at some point.
But this is the spider place.
No.
Rectangle, please.
Looky...
Layer.
I hate that place.
And that connects like that.
Pretty cool, huh?
Okay.
Let's see, we also need to fill out the ancient laboratory and stuff.
But we can do that next time when we go there.
That's the plan.
Yep.
Didn't I also find something else?
Fungal Cavern.
This one is pretty much...
Oh wait, it's not a tablet that's in here.
This is actually a book.
So I did that wrong.
I need to recolor that a little bit.
Hold on.
That can be, like, a color of...
brown?
Brownish?
Something like that.
That's a book.
It's a little bit hard to see, but that's okay.
I just want to distinguish it for myself later.
Okay, that looks good.
Okay, people.
Back to this screen right here.
How we doing, huh?
Cheers.
I hope you're having a wonderful Sunday, everybody.
This was a great stream, man.
I had so much fun.
I slept and woke up and you were still playing?
That's right, damn it.
I'm a real gamer.
I love the Hamis thumbs up.
This was a bit of an impromptu, pretty long stream, I guess.
I wasn't planning on streaming this long.
I just had fun, man.
What can I say?
Completely forgot the time while watching.
Same.
Except playing, you know?
I also forgot the time completely.
Glad to see I could catch this beginning and end of this despite my sleep.
Nice.
Well, you actually did well because the very middle of this was not as entertaining, I feel like.
It was the end and the start that was the best of this stream.
So you got the best parts.
I did a lot of dying in the middle there.
It's my and Hive's birthday today.
Only arrived at seven hours though.
Is it though?
Is that true?
Is it actually?
Hmm.
Okay, I'm going to believe it.
Happy birthday.
How many times around the sun have you been?
Light night.
I'll make a list of useful emotes in this court.
Maybe you can add some of them.
Yes, awesome.
Please.
If you want to see a cool emote, suggest them there.
I'm going to take a look at them.
I think I'm probably going to split this VOD into two pieces just because it's so long.
And put it on YouTube.
This run is so lucky and you're also not using anything.
It's both fun and frustrating to watch.
I imagine.
I mean, I think I'm using as much as I can, of course.
I mean, from my perspective, I think I'm doing as good as I can, right?
But obviously there are still things you're going to miss.
And that's fine.
You always get lucky with those random ass spider tunnels.
Do I really?
A low-key blessing.
Game gave you five different ways to go up, but when you ignore them, it just gave you...
Wait, really?
I have no idea what those were.
Don't tell me, though.
I'll probably find out later and have a good laugh about it when I finally discover it.
That's going to be a fun time.
You love the low-key?
Man, I hate them.
I can't stand it.
When I can kill them, then I'm fine.
As long as I can get rid of them, then I'm cool, you know?
I just don't want them next to me, near me, anywhere near.
The game loves and hates you at the same time?
I believe that.
Are you perhaps open to doing a daily run next?
People have said that it may contain a bit of spoilers or some things that shouldn't be there in the game because I haven't unlocked them yet.
I mean, I am open to it.
If people think it's fine and there's not a lot of stuff that's going to be weird for me, then it's probably okay.
I mean, it's not going to be much different, right?
It's just going to be a seed that everyone else has on the same day.
It contains all spells, but no major spoilers.
Yeah, okay.
That could be fun.
There's also a Twitch integration.
I know about that.
But people have told me I shouldn't use it yet because it would detract from the beginner experience of Noiter, you know?
So I'm still absorbing the game as it is.
But I definitely want to do the integration as well as at some point.
And then I actually be interactive with chat as well.
I think both sort of need to happen.
I think that would be fun.
Should we finish the prediction?
It doesn't transfer to the next stream, right?
I don't know what prediction you have made.
How do I see that?
I mean, it's up to you.
Honestly, you decide that.
That's totally fine.
Okay, guys, I'm going to go now and I'm going to release another Prey video for you guys.
So I'm going to send you off to another Noiter streamer.
Let's see who's online.
Let's make their day, huh?
If we can.
Well, or make their next five minutes.
Let's see what we got.
There's a guy called Tango Milk who has a stream called Noiter Novice Edition.
I feel like that's very... I actually love seeing that.
I kind of want more people to play this game now, you know, because I think it's so cool.
I'm going to send you off.
I want to say thank you all for watching.
This was a long-ass stream.
I had a lot of fun.
I hope you did too.
Thanks for subscribing and following and just watching, hanging out.
I appreciate it.
Come join the Discord and check out my YouTube channel if you're new here.
All right, I'm off.
Have a good one, guys.
Bye-bye.